Are you there?
你在吗?
I'm here.
我在
Help me. My client is going to jail.
帮我,我的客户要蹲大牢了
Oh, no, she's not.
不,她不会的
I think I've got it.
我想我已经搞清楚了
Really?
真的?
Look up Hasson v. Conrad.
去查一下哈森对康拉德案
Similar circumstantial evidence...
相似的间接证据...
case was thrown out.
官司却打赢了
Legaleagle, thank you.
法鹰,谢谢你
You are by far the most brilliant mind
你是这个聊天室里
in this chat room.
最最聪明的人
Thank you, Lawyer-girl.
谢谢你,律师姑娘
I realize we have certain anonymity here,
我知道我们在这里都是匿名的
but do you, by any chance, have a name?
但是,你会不会碰巧有个名字呢?
It's Charlene.
我叫夏琳
I missed you yesterday.
昨天我想你了
How was your day?
你过得怎么样?
Uneventful.
平平常常
I exercised for an hour in the morning,
早上出去运动了一个小时
poked around in the yard in the afternoon,
下午在院子里散了一会步
and visited with a girlfriend down the block in the evening.
晚上去拜访住在附近的一个女友
Sounds innocent enough.
听起来很单纯啊
Don't let my humdrum day fool you, now.
不要被我的单调的一天蒙蔽了哦
I also have a very dark side.
我也有非常阴暗的一面
Well, I'm 31
我今年31岁5个月零6天
with long, flowing locks and an athletic body.
留着披肩长发,身材健美
Peter, what do you look like?
彼德,你长什么样?
I'm... a little older... 6'2".
我...比你年纪大一点...6个月零2天
My hair is... it's light.
我的发色...很浅
Uh, it's boyishly light.
是那种很稚气的浅色
And good night to you, Lawyer-girl.
也祝你晚安,律师姑娘
Gendler.
钱德勒
- Good morning, Mr. Sanderson. - Hi.
早,山德森先生 嗨
Morning, Peter.
早,彼德
How are you?
你好
Gentlemen.
先生们
Oh, good. Peter's here. We can begin.
好,彼德来了,我们可以开始了
Okay. On to pressing business.
好的 根据新闻媒体报导
Word has come to us
我们听到消息
that coffee heiress Mrs. Virginia Arness
那个大咖啡公司的继承人 维吉妮雅亚妮丝夫人
has dismissed her current tax lawyers.
已经解雇了她现在的税务律师团
Virginia Arness.
维吉妮雅亚妮丝
74 years old, born and raised in Athens, Georgia.
74岁,生于乔治亚州雅典市并在那里长大
At the age of 13,
她十三岁的时候
she was shipped off to boarding school in England,
被送往英国读寄宿学校
where she's been residing until just recently.
并且住在那里直到最近
That was only two days ago.
也就是两天前
Impressive.
精彩
Now, we've all heard
我们都听说了
that Mrs. Arness has a penchant for thriftiness.
亚妮丝夫人非常之节俭
And that she brings new meaning to the term "conservative."
她的行为给"保守"一词带来了新的含义
It's not going to be easy.
这件是不会那么简单
She's paranoid and suspicious. Peter...
她既偏执又多疑,彼德...
I'm her guy.
我去最合适
I'm single. I'll give her nights, weekends.
我是单身,我晚上、周末都可以去找她
Aren't you getting married on Sunday, Todd?
你不是这个周日要结婚的吗,陶德?
That's flexible.
婚期可以推迟的
And, Peter, I wouldn't want this to interfere
还有,彼德,我不想让这件事影响到
with your family's Hawaiian vacation.
你和家人一起去夏威夷渡假
You go on.
你尽管放心去
I got it all taken care of.
一切包在我身上
Mahalo.
谢谢
Well, that's very admirable of you, Todd.
你能这样想我非常感谢,陶德
I mean, your youth definitely makes you an ass...
我是说,你的年轻当然会让你成为...
...et to the company,
...公司的宝贵财产
especially at the annual softball game.
尤其是每年的垒球比赛
But to an archconservative, 74-year-old woman?
但是对付一个极端保守的 74岁的老太太恐怕差点
What will we do is not charge Mrs. Arness one single red cent
我们要做的是不收亚妮丝夫人一毛钱
for her estate planning.
为她做好不动产计划
Why?
为什么?
Because we don't care about that measly fee.
因为我们不在乎那点小钱
We use it as a loss leader to get her corporate business,
我们可以以此来争揽她们公司的业务
the multibillion-dollar Arness coffee conglomerate.
亚妮丝咖啡集团可是资产 数十亿美元的大公司
How may I help you, Howie?
有什么要我帮忙的吗,郝威?
Just thought I'd congratulate you on turning it around.
我只是想来恭喜你扭转乾坤
Turning what around?
扭转什么乾坤?
You snaked Gendler.
你打败了钱德勒
Please. Gendler doesn't bother me.
拜托.我从来都没把钱德勒放在眼里
Oh, that's right. He doesn't bother you.
哦,对对,你没把他放在眼里
What the heck was I thinking?
我在想什么呢?
Listen, I thought maybe after work
我想下班后
you and me go tie one on,
我们是不是去喝点酒
maybe check out some of the local talent.
顺便看看本地有什么天才
Can't. I'm meeting Mrs. Arness at 6:00.
不行,我6点钟要去见亚妮丝夫人
And by the way, it's "You and I go tie one on,"
顺便说一下,是"你和我去喝酒"
not "You and me go."
不是"你和我去"
Somebody messaging you here.
有人在给你发消息
Who's Lawyer-girl?
谁是律师姑娘?
Nobody.
谁都不是
Whoa. Did someone make a blind Internet date?
哇,你不会想去跟网友见面吧?
No. I mean, you know, well, technically, but no.
不.我是说,你知道的 技术上说是的,但是不是
I met her in a legal chat room.
我跟她是在一个法律专题聊天室里碰到的
She's, uh, very classy and smart.
她是,呃,非常聪明非常有品味的
When do you nail her?
你上她了吗?
I'm courting her tonight at 7:00.
今天晚上7点我去追求她
Oh, jeez. You're courting her. Sounds like a hot one.
哦,天,你在追求她,听起来很刺激
And this is her?
这就是她?
Yeah, she's attractive, isn't she?
是的,她很迷人,对不对?
I suppose. It's not my cup of tea.
我想是,不是我喜欢的类型
What do you... she is universally cute.
什么啊...她绝对是人见人爱的大美人
Eh, she's a little too anemic-Iooking, Petey.
呃,她看起来有点太贫血了
I like my jello to jiggle, if I'm not being too subtle.
要不是我身体弱肯定会喜欢那个的
You're not being too subtle.
你身体还行啊
All right, as long as she spins your knobs, I'm happy for you.
好了,只要她让你开心,我就替你感到高兴了
Have you nailed anyone since Kate?
除了凯特你还有没有上过其他人?
Nail... I was supposed to call her.
上...我该打电话给她了
Sofia, can you get my wife on the phone?
苏菲亚,帮我打电话给我老婆好吧?
- Ex-wife. - Ex-wife on the phone?
前妻 对,前妻
Right away.
马上就打
Can't help you with this one, pal. See you later.
这个我帮不了你,伙计,回头见
Peter, you cannot break another promise to these kids.
彼德,你不能再对孩子们食言了
You just can't.
你就是不能
I said I couldn't take them to Hawaii.
我只是说我不能带他们去夏威夷
I didn't say I couldn't take them.
并没有说不能陪他们啊
They can spend the week with me.
他们这星期可以跟我
They are gonna be so disappointed.
他们会很失望的
I can't talk to you right now.
我现在不能跟你长谈
Um... Daddy can't take you to Hawaii.
爸爸不能带你们去夏威夷了
Oh, darn.
哦,该死
He always does this.
他总是这样
Sanderson, party of two.
山德森,订了两个人的位子
Oh, you're the last to arrive.
哦,你来得有点迟
How long has she been here?
她来了多久了?
Mmm, about 20 minutes.
大概有20分钟
Was she trouble?
她麻烦吗?
Thank you.
谢谢
Hello. I'm Peter Sanderson.
你好.我是彼德山德森
Well, I'm glad they didn't send a child.
好,很高兴他们没有派个小孩过来
I told them I specifically wanted someone my own age.
我特别要求他们派人跟我年纪相仿的人
What a wonderful French bulldog.
多好的法国牛头犬啊
My mother had one. They make great companions.
我母亲曾经养过一个,非常好的伙伴
What's her name?
她叫什么名字?
His name is William Shakespeare.
他叫威廉莎士比亚
Well, of course.
哦,当然
Now, I've heard about your unfortunate escapade.
我听说了你的不幸的脱逃
I don't have escapades.
我没有脱逃
Fiasco with your previous attorney.
我是说解雇你以前的那个律师
The man was a thieving criminal.
那个家伙是个强盗
Just because I have a lot of money
不能因为我有很多钱
doesn't give people the right to overcharge.
人们就有权来给我出高价啊
I do not enjoy being taken advantage of.
我不喜欢被人占便宜
Which is why our service is free of charge.
所以我们才免费为您服务
After all, you worked hard for your money.
无论如何,你的钱都是辛苦挣来的
I'm an heiress.
是继承来的
An heiress who worked hard to keep her money.
哦,继承来的也要辛苦保值啊
Now, shall we get down to business?
现在我们能谈正事了吗?
Fine.
好
So, now you may hand over your proposal.
那你可能把建议书给我了
I'll take it with me.
我带着走
Proposal?
建议书?
Well, I was expecting to meet with you tomorrow.
我准备明天见面再给你的
I was assured the proposal would be ready
有人向我保证今天下午
for this afternoon.
建议书就能搞好的
I see no point in our meeting tomorrow.
我觉得明天我们根本没有必要见面
Excuse me. Madam, I'm sorry.
打扰一下,夫人,对不起
We have a no-dog policy in the lounge.
我们这里不允许带狗的
Unfortunately, I'm gonna have to ask you to remove the dog.
非常抱歉,我得请您把狗带走
Excuse me. I am Mrs. Arness' attorney,
对不起,我是亚妮丝夫人的律师
and because there is no sign posted regarding dogs,
因为这里并没有挂禁止带狗的标牌
that means there is no policy toward dogs.
所以这里就没有允不允许带狗的规矩
Now, if you want to avoid a legal situation,
如果你不想吃官司的话
I would suggest you run to the kitchen
我建议你赶快跑去厨房
and get some tuna tartare for William Shakespeare
去给这里的威廉莎士比亚
on the house.
弄点鲔鱼酱料来
Yes, sir.
是,先生
I'm terribly sorry, ma'am.
非常抱歉,夫人
Where and when tomorrow?
明天几点什么时候见面?
Hello, Mr. Sanderson.
你好,山德森先生
Oh, Mrs. Kline. Always a pleasure.
克莱恩夫人,见到你永远都是一种荣幸
And when am I going to get to babysit
我什么时候能再去
with your charming little Georgey again?
照顾你家迷人的小乔治?
Oh, uh, well, uh, soon,
很快了
because he just loves coming over to your place.
因为他很喜欢去你家玩
Uh, Mr. Sanderson?
呃,山德森先生?
Those Latin people who were skulking around...
那些鬼鬼崇崇的拉丁人...
Oh. They were looking at the Aruda house.
哦,他们在找阿鲁达的房子
Casing it?
给房子装管道?
No, uh, to buy it.
不,是要买下来
Oh, please.
哦,拜托
If they're in this block and not carrying a leaf blower...
如果他们在这区而不带吹落叶机...
Yeah.
是啊
Well, I'd love to discuss this with you further,
我非常想继续跟你讨论这个问题
but I'm expecting someone.
但是我还约了人
Hey.
嗨
Hi.
你好
I hope you like cham...
希望你喜欢香...
...poo.
...波
What's up, baby?
怎么了,宝贝?
Ooh, champagne. I love champagne.
哦,香槟,我喜欢香槟
This for me?
这是为我准备的?
Oh, I'm sorry. I think you have the wrong house.
对不起.我想你是走错地方了
It is damn good to finally connect.
终于见面了,真他妈的好
Pardon me?
什么?
It's me, fool... Charlene.
是我啊,傻瓜...夏琳
Ooh, food.
哦,吃的
What?
什么?
It's me, honey. Your date... Lawyer-girl.
是我啊,亲爱的 你约会的对象...律师姑娘
You can't be.
不可能
Hey, hey, hey. Leave that alone.
别碰那个
Well, why can't I?
为什么我不能是?
Because you're not a blonde.
因为你不是金发
Can't get nothing past you.
怎么都骗不到你
You must be a bomb-ass lawyer.
你肯定是个很棒的律师
Oh, look at all of these pretty candles...
哦,看看这些漂亮的蜡烛
all romantic and shit.
浪漫死了
Somebody was planning on getting some booty tonight.
有人准备今晚有所斩获啊
Hey! Leave that alone. There are settings.
嗨!别碰那个,那个是设好了的
And you can't be Charlene, because Charlene is more of...
你不可能是夏琳,因为夏琳是那种...
Skinny white broad?
瘦瘦的小白人?
Yeah.
是的
You know, I get that a lot.
知道吗,我经常听人家那么说
But that's your fault you're thinking that, bro.
但你那么想是你自己的错,兄弟
You must have not have took a good look at that picture.
你肯定没有仔细看那张照片
I have looked at that picture a lot,
那张照片我看了很多次
and trust me, you are not in it.
相信我,你不在里面
Move, move, move. Let me do it.
让开,让我来
See?
看到了?
There I am.
我就在那儿
Sorry you got it twisted, dog.
对不起你搞混了
I don't get a lot of photo ops where I been.
我当时在的地方没有多少照片
Where exactly have you been?
你当时究竟在什么地方?
I got a rumble in the jungle. We still having dinner or what?
我去林子里转了一圈 我们还准备吃晚餐吗?
I asked you a question.
我在问你问题呢
Rolex.
劳力士
Rolex?
劳力士?
I did time, baby, but I ain't do the crime.
我坐过牢,宝贝,但是我没有犯罪
You're a convict?
你是个罪犯?
Bump that.
别乱讲
Shoot, Roscoe cracked that door.
罗斯柯破坏那道门
I kicked it off the heezy and bounced.
我踢开门而已
For real, though.
真的
What did you just say?
我刚才说什么?
What, don't you hear good?
什么,你耳朵不好吗?
All right.
好吧
Let's see. How can I put this?
让我想想,我该怎么说呢?
I was recently liberated from a correctional facility...
我最近刚被释放出来...
All right. I get it.
好了,我知道了
You're in the big house, and you get someone to type for you,
你在坐牢,然后你找人帮你打字
and you get on the Internet, and you misrepresent yourself.
然后你上了网,对别人撒谎
It happens, and I'm a sucker,
居然碰到这种事,我真倒霉
but now you have to go, because this is over.
现在你得走了,因为一切都结束了
Unh-unh. No, no, no.
不不不
Biscuit, you misrepresented yourself.
亲爱的,你才撒谎了呢
Boyishly light... please.
稚气的浅色...拜托
Gray.
是灰色
You said you was a criminal lawyer.
你说你是罪案律师
I pulled your file.
我查过你的档案
You're just some sorry-ass tax attorney.
你只不过是个可怜的税务律师
A tax lawyer is a criminal lawyer.
税务律师就是罪案律师
Oh, yeah?
哦,是吗?
Well, good, 'cause that's why I'm here.
那好,因为这就是我来的目的
Well, do tell.
告诉我
Well, I want to reopen my case.
我想重新审理我的案子
And what did you do, smoke some homies on a drive-by?
那你做了什么 在车道护栏上点烟烧房子吗?
Smoke? Homies?
点烟? 烧房子?
Well, you a regular gangster, huh?
你是个职业罪犯,呃?
No, man. I was in for armed robbery, but I didn't do it.
不,伙计,我因为持枪抢劫而入狱 但是我没有干过
Yeah, nobody did it.
是啊,没有人动过手
I can't be having this conversation
我不能跟你谈这个
because you're a criminal-type.
因为你是会犯罪的那种人
If I was a criminal, I would have shanked you
如果我是罪犯的话
when I had that knife in my hand.
早就拿那把刀杀了你了
The fact that you even said that is a problem for me.
你这种说法让我很不安
- But I didn't think that. - It's just time to go.
但我没有那种想法 你该走了
Please, just listen to me. Just give me one second.
拜托,听我说,一秒钟就好
No, I don't have a second.
不,我没有一秒钟给你
Okay, can I just say something, please?
那让我说几句话,行不行?
What?
什么?
I didn't do the crime.
我没犯法
You rude mother...
你粗鲁的混...
I ain't goin'.
我不会走的
It's your baby, Peter, and don't you deny it!
那是你的孩子,彼德,别不承认!
That DNA test told on you!
DNA测试都证明了的!
You lie, Peter!
你是个骗子,彼德!
You know lil' Kareem is yours!
你知道小卡林是你的!
Why?!
为什么?!
How you gonna do me like that, Peter?!
你怎么能这样对我,彼德?!
You told me I was your beautiful African Queen.
你跟我说过我是你的非洲皇后的
And I loved you for that, Peter!
因为那个我才爱上了你,彼德!
I didn't care if your little thing was curved.
我不在乎你的小东西是不是弯曲的
And lil' Kareem don't want your child support.
而且小卡林也不指望你养活
He just want a relationship with his white daddy.
他只是想跟他的白种爸爸保持父子关系
A little chocolate/vanilla swirl
一点点巧克力香草双淇淋
from that magical night at the crackhouse.
皆源自破屋那奇妙的一夜
Oh!
哦!
Come on. Just be quiet!
进屋吧,只要安静点!
Wait just a second. My shoes.
等一下,我的鞋掉了
- Mr. Sanderson? - Whoa!
山德森先生? 哇哦!
Is everything okay?
没事吧?
I thought I heard Negro.
我想我听到黑鬼的声音了
No. No Negro spoken here.
不,这里没有黑鬼
Oh.
哦
Well... good night, then.
那...晚安
Oh, uh...
哦,呃...
good night.
晚安
Come on!
进去!
Come on, come on!
快,快!
You stay. You stay. You wait right there.
你别动,就在那里等着
Who you callin'?
你在打电话给谁?
The police.
警察
Police department. Sergeant Panella. Please hold.
警察局,潘尼拉警官,请稍等
What's that?
那是什么?
It's all of our e-mails.
是我们所有的电子邮件
You think anybody at Tobias, Kline, and Barnes
你想托拜尔斯、克莱恩和巴恩斯哪一个
would be interested in hearing
会有兴趣听...
about you looking for Boom-boom in the federal pen?
关于你在聊天室找一夜情的事呢?
And I'll send a photo.
我还会寄张照片
Thanks for holding. Can I help you?
谢谢您的等待.有什么可以效劳的?
Now, this is just for tonight, understand?
只有今天一晚,明白吗?
A'ight.
好
I can work with this.
我能忍受这个
But, uh, look, don't be gettin' no ideas
但是想都不要想
about sneakin' up in here and hittin' this ass,
偷偷进来占我的便宜
'cause you blew your chance with this fine sister.
因为你已经失去了与 这位漂亮妹妹一起的机会了
Dare to dream.
你做梦
Tsk. Please.
拜托
Oh, my God! A bed!
哦,我的上帝!床!
Oh, a nice, big, cushy bed.
又大又舒服的床
Ohh, no roommates, no cellmates.
哦,没有室友,也没有牢友
Charlene?
夏琳?
Charlene.
夏琳
Charlene! Come on, you're not fooling anybody.
夏琳! 算啦,你能骗得了谁啊
Who that? Who there?
谁啊?谁在那儿?
Who want it with Lene?
谁想找琳的麻烦?
I put some bagels outside.
我在外面放了些百吉卷
I thought we could discuss your case.
我想我们可以出去讨论一下你的案子
What up, dog? Where 'em bagels at?
怎么了?百吉卷呢?
Hey, guess what, girlfriend? Your game is up.
你猜怎么样,女朋友? 你的游戏结束了
Because I burned all those e-mails,
因为我烧掉了所有的电子邮件
including the second set hidden in the lining of your coat.
包括藏在你外套衬里里的那份
And I deleted everything off my computer.
我还删除了我电脑上的所有东西
So I never met you, and you never met me.
所以我从来没见过你,你也从未见过我
Don't even try, girlfriend, because it's locked.
想都不要想,女朋友,因为门锁上了
And now I am going to go get my kids,
现在我要去接我的孩子
as in innocent young persons
对这些纯真的孩子而言
who will never even know you were here.
你从来都没有来过这里
So now just go.
所以,请你马上离开
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
走,走,走,走,走!
And locky locky!
然后锁上门!
And watch out. The gate closes automatically.
注意,门会自动关上的
Well, what about my stuff?
那你把我的东西放哪儿了?
Oh, it's right there on the street.
哦,就在那边的街上
You put my stuff on the trash?
你把我的东西放在垃圾桶上?
Oh. Well, you know what?
哦,你知道吗?
I wish you well. I really do.
祝你好运,真的
And you know what? I had a great, great time.
还有,我真的度过了一段非常愉快的时光
It was really fun.
非常有意思
So, oh, well.
那,哦,好了
I guess I'll just see you in my next life.
我想我们来生再见吧
Heh heh heh heh. Bye!
哈哈哈哈哈,再见!
Ha ha. I'll see you when you get home.
哈哈,你回家就能见到我
So I said to him,
所以我跟他说
"Just 'cause you whisked me to Paris on your private jet
"不要以为我坐了你的飞机去了趟巴黎"
doesn't mean I'm gonna sleep with you."
"就一定要跟你睡觉"
What does he think I am? A hooker?
他以为我是什么人?妓女?
Can Aunt Ashley edit herself, please?
艾希莉阿姨会乱编吗? 拜托
You stayed in the same room with him.
你跟他住在同一间房里
What did you expect?
你以为会发生什么事?
Hello. It was a suite... plenty of floor space.
拜托.那是个套房...地方大着呢
Sweetiepie, have a wonderful time. I love you.
宝贝,好好玩,我爱你
Please be good to your brother and help him with his reading.
对你弟弟好一点,带他读书
- I will. - Thank you.
我会的 谢谢
Is he still having problems?
他还有问题吗?
Oh, he struggles every day, but he's improving.
哦,他每天都在拚命,但是还有点进步
Dad's here.
爸爸来了
Thank you, sweetiepie.
谢谢你,宝贝
Don't worry, sweetie.
别担心,宝贝
Daddy's stupid, too, and he became a lawyer.
爸爸也很蠢,不也是做了律师嘛
Ashley!
艾希莉!
I'm not stupid.
我不蠢
- That's right. - No, no, no. Of course not.
对了 不,不,不,当然不是
Hey, Dad's here.
嗨,爸爸到了
Speak of the dummy.
说曹操曹操到
Hey, how's my little girl doin', huh?
嗨,我的小姑娘过得怎么样,啊?
Hi, Dad.
你好,爸爸
Hey, how's it goin', big guy?
你过得怎样啊,大家伙?
Ahhh, here you go.
啊,抱住你了
Hi, Kate.
你好,凯特
Hi.
你好
Oh, Ashley, I didn't realize you were gonna be here.
艾希莉,没想到你会在这里
What a pleasant surprise.
真是个惊喜
Peter, you're almost aging well.
彼德,你都快熟透了
Okay, I thought we'd go down to the club and take a swim.
好了,我们去俱乐部游泳吧
Ooh, that sounds much more fun than Maui.
哦,那听起来比去毛伊岛好玩多了
You know, Ashley, not all of us earn our living
知道吗,艾希莉,不是所有人
by milking rich geriatrics out of their money.
都能靠傍老大款赚钱的
Some of us have to work for a living.
有些人是必须要靠工作养活自己的
You sound much more intelligent with your mouth shut.
你不说话会显得聪明得多
Let's not start this. I don't have time.
别吵,我没时间了
Kids, go get your stuff.
孩子们,把你们的东西拿上
All right, fine.
好吧
But I warned you
但是我警告过你
about marrying the first jerk-off you met out of college.
不要跟你毕业后碰到的第一个混蛋结婚
Now, if you'll excuse me, I have a date.
现在,请原谅,我有个约会要参加
Don't be good.
别对他太好
What morgue did you find this one at?
你要约的这家伙是在哪个太平间碰到的?
Stop being so childish.
别这么孩子气
Hey.
嗨
Wow. You look beautiful.
你真美
Thank you.
谢谢
Uh, Peter, this is Glen.
彼德,这位是葛伦
Hey.
嗨
Hey, Mr. Sanderson. Nice to see you.
嗨,山德森先生 很高兴见到你
Yeah, nice to meet you.
是啊,很高兴见到你
Uh, what do you say we get this road on the show?
我们出去兜风怎么样?
Okay.
好啊
I will meet you outside.
我在外面等你
Road on the show.
兜风
Just don't.
别这样
How old is he?
他多大?
Younger.
比我小
- What does he do? - Golf instructor.
他是干什么的? 教高尔夫球的
- How do you know that? - What?
你怎么知道的? 什么?
Well, you think you know somebody,
你以为你了解某个人
and then one day you wake up in Thailand missing a kidney.
然后有天你会在泰国醒来 发现自己少了一个肾
He could have made up this whole golf identity.
他的所谓高尔夫教练的身份 可能是编造出来的
He caddied for you when he was 14.
他14岁的时候给你泡过茶
That's little Glenny?
那个就是小葛伦?
Does that bother you?
你有什么意见吗?
Not at all.
一点都没有
Go have fun on your statutory weekend.
在你的法定假日你好好玩玩吧
This does too bother you. I know you.
你肯定有意见,我了解你
Do you want to talk about it?
你想谈谈这个吗?
Well, it just looks a little silly.
只不过看起来有点蠢的样子
Hang on.
等一下
Hello?
喂?
Some things never change.
有些事永远都不会变
I can't talk right now.
我现在不方便说话
Well, put him on.
好吧,把电话接过来
Hi.
你好
You promised us you'd take us snorkeling.
你答应带我们去潜水的
Things come up. That's life.
有事情要做了,生活就是这样
I know. I'm really, really sorry.
我知道,我真的非常对不起
But now it's over. It's new. We're gonna have a lot of fun.
但现在结束了,新的开始 我们会很开心的
Now, what's new? What's new with you?
有什么新鲜事?你有什么新鲜事?
Well, I got the female lead in the school play "Oklahoma!"
我在学校出演话剧"奥克拉荷马"女主角
Hey, that's great. Congratulations.
棒极了,恭喜
And how 'bout you, big guy? How's school?
你呢,大家伙?学校怎么样?
I don't like school.
我不喜欢学校
Well, nobody likes school,
没有人喜欢学校
but there must be something you like about it.
但是学校里面总有你喜欢的东西吧
He got into a fight the other day.
有天他在学校里打架了
Why? Why'd you get in a fight?
为什么?为什么要打架?
Some kids called me a baby 'cause of the way I read.
有人说我读书的样子像个婴儿
Some of the greatest minds of all time had trouble learning,
有很多大人物学习都有困难的
like Edgar Allan Poe and Albert Einstein
像艾德加爱伦坡和爱因斯坦
and, uh, Ozzy Osbourne.
还有,欧西奥兹朋
Ozzy rules.
欧西不算
Ozzy rules. Okay.
欧西不算,好的
Dad, what's goin' on?
爸爸,出什么事了?
You two wait here. I'll be right back.
你们俩在这里等,我马上回来
Hey!
嗨!
Whoa, whoa. Where you think you're goin', milk?
你以为你是要去哪儿,牛奶?
This here's a charitable event.
里面正在进行慈善活动
You wants to get in, you gots to make a donation.
要想进去,请先捐款
Trust me, it is off the hook in there.
相信我,里头脱离险境了
Off the what? I live here.
脱离什么?我住在这里
I don't care if you're Halle Berry, man.
我不管你是不是哈利贝瑞,伙计
No donation, no entry.
不捐款,就别想进去
How 'bout if I call the police?
那我报警怎么样?
Have a nice time.
进去好好玩吧
Yeah, baby, show me.
好啊,宝贝,让我看看
Hey! What the hell is going on here?
你们到底在干什么?
Oh, yo, P., it's cool.
哦,没事的
See, I hit up my homegirl
我找了我的女友
'cause I had to get my hair done, as we both know.
因为我得去做做头发
And then she called a friend. They holler to other friends.
然后她就叫了个朋友 他们又找了他们的朋友
Before you know it, we got us a house par-ty.
不知不觉中就成了家庭聚会了
I want everyone out of here now!
我要你们所有人都出去!
People!
大伙听着!
Loosen your panties, Grandma.
放松一点,娘娘腔
Look, you lock me out, no money, no place to go.
你把我锁在外面,没钱,没地方去
I mean, a girl got to get her cheese on.
我是说,女孩子就要开开心心的
This is insane!
这简直是疯了!
My boss' sister lives across the street.
我老板的姐姐就住在街对面
I can't have all these peop...
我不能让这些人...
Hey!
嗨!
Give me a hard seven, baby.
给我来个7,宝贝!
She doesn't even have her driver's permit.
她连驾照都还没拿到
Dad.
爸爸
Do not go...
不要去...
Roll! Uh!
掷!
Don't inhale.
别吸气
All right, now. Go on and toss them bones, lil' man.
好啦,继续把他们的油水榨干,小家伙
Hey! Give me...
嗨!给我...
I'm on a roll, Dad.
轮到我掷了,爸爸
Get out.
出去
I want you and your dogs to go back to the pound now.
我要你跟你的狗们滚回你们的狗窝去
What?
什么?
Well, it was the dogs?
什么,是因为我说狗的吗?
Because she said dogs, and then I said dogs,
因为她说过狗的,我以为我说狗
so I assumed that would be okay.
你们不会介意的
Huh?
啊?
Bye, Tamika. Y'all be good, now.
再见,塔米卡,你们好好照顾自己
Bye.
再见
Hey, hey. Y'all got to go.
你们都得走了
- A'ight. - That's a'ight.
好吧 那好吧
Hey, baby, gonna go.
嗨,宝贝,我得走了
Oh, bye, Bear. Thank you so much.
哦,再见,小熊 非常感谢
Party's over. Okay. Thanks for coming.
聚会结束了,好了,感谢光临
But that's it. It's over.
但是已经结束了
If I see Widow around, I'm gonna tell him you're out.
如果我看到威多的话 我会告诉他你已经出来了
You know he wants to know that.
你知道他想知道那个
I don't know about that. I'll see you.
这我倒不知道,我会再找你的
- Okay. Bye, baby. - Bye-bye.
好的,再见,宝贝 再见
It's like this.
是像这样的
Hey.
嗨
- How you doin', neighbor? - What's up?
过得怎么样,邻居? 怎么了?
What are you still doing here?
你还在这里做什么?
- What was all that, Dad? - Dad, who's this?
那些都是什么人啊,爸爸? 爸爸,这是谁啊?
This is no one.
她谁都不是
Tsk! What's up, lil' Romeo?
怎么了,小罗蜜欧?
My name is Charlene. What's your name?
我叫夏琳,你叫什么名字?
I'm Georgey.
我叫乔治
You cannot meet a nonexistent person.
你不能与一个不存在的人说话
Can Charlene come to the club?
夏琳会跟我们一起去俱乐部吗?
Club? What club?
俱乐部?什么俱乐部?
We're not going to a club, remember?
我们没准备去什么俱乐部,记得吗?
We're going to Hawaii,
我们要去夏威夷的,记得吗?
Okay, you know the routine. Outski!
好了,你知道该怎么做了,出去!!!
- Out! Let's go. - Come on, man!
出去!快走. 别这样,伙计!
Sarah, get the door. Come on. Out.
莎拉,把门打开.快,出去
Out, out, out!
出去,出去,出去!
- Wait! - What?
等等! 什么?
Give me my money, lil' boy.
把我的钱给我,小家伙
That money should go to charity!
那些钱应该捐给慈善机构的!
Ohh!
哦!
What did...
你到底想...
Hey, I live here.
嗨,我住在这里
Yeah!
耶!
What?
什么?
Okay, you guys.
好了,大家
You know, you order hot dogs, and you splash and frolic
你们尽管点些热狗,然后尽情的玩水
and just put everything on my account and just have fun.
所有东西都记在我的帐上好了 只要玩得开心就好
Didn't you bring your bathing suit?
你没带浴衣来吗?
Oh, no. I'm having tea with a client.
哦,不,我要跟一个客户去喝茶
But I will be right back.
但是我很快就会回来的
Whatever you say.
随你怎么说
Want to go swimming?
想去游泳吗?
With you?
和你?
Forget you.
算了吧
How's it looking?
看起来怎么样?
Well, I was up all night proofing.
我一整晚都在证明
It's absolutely brilliant.
你的计划是绝对明智的
And you've got the cleanest background check I've ever seen.
你有着我见过的最干净的背景
That background check cost me a lot of fun in my life.
那种背景让我失去了生命中的很多乐趣
I don't know, honey.
我不知道,亲爱的
Don't say anything. She could hear you.
什么都别说,她会听见的
What's crackin', ma?
那么吃惊干什么?
I'm lookin' for the Sanderson table.
我在找山德森的桌子
We old college buddies.
我们是大学时代的老同学
O-O-Okay. He's i-in the dining room.
好...好的,他在餐厅里
I-I'll show you.
我带你去
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
哦,不不不不
I tell you what... I'll surprise him.
我跟你说...我要给他一个惊喜
No, you're in great shape. I'm gonna take off.
不,你现在情况很好.我要走了
All right, you're right. Nothing could go wrong.
好的,你是对的,什么都不可能出错
I've done this a million times with important clients,
我跟重要客户会面至少也要上百万次了
so I'm fine.
所以我没事
- Shazam. - What?
快变 什么?
Oh, no.
哦,不
Oh, swing it, you cocoa goddess.
完了 你这个可可女神
Cocoa Goddess? That's the rude shock I was telling you about.
可可女神? 那就是我跟你说的 粗鲁的女人
That's Charlene?
那就是夏琳?
Did she see me?
她看到我了吗?
Okay, okay, okay, police.
好好好,报警
Uh, no. Won't get here fast enough.
呃,不,来不及了
Uh, security.
呃,叫保安
No, she could probably take him.
恐怕打不过她
Uh, money.
呃,钱
She'll take money.
她会要钱的
Hi, hi. Here, just... Here's whatever.
你好,给你,这些都给你
And there's more where that came from if you just leave now.
如果你现在就走的话 我以后还会给你更多
No. Unh-unh, boyfriend. We got business.
不,男朋友,我们有事要谈
Boyfriend?
男朋友?
Oh, didn't I tell you? We're dating now.
哦,我没跟你说过吗?我们在约会
It's some kind of street talk.
是某种街语
It's street for "I'm not going nowhere
是说"在你帮我解决我的问题之前"
until you help my problem go away."
"我哪儿都不会去"
Look, Mrs. Arness, a very important client,
听说,亚妮丝夫人,一个非常重要的客户
is due here any minute.
随时都可能来
Good afternoon.
下午好
Mr. Sanderson?
下午好,山德森先生?
Oh, yes. He's in the dining room.
哦,是,他在餐厅
Thank you.
谢谢
Charlene, how 'bout you and I
夏琳,你看我们能不能
havin' a smart cocktail down by the pool?
一起去泳池边去喝点鸡尾酒?
Who is this fool?
这个傻瓜是谁?
That's a good idea. Just put it on my bill.
好主意,记在我的帐上好了
I don't want no smart cocktail. I need your help.
我不想喝什么鸡尾酒,我需要你的帮助
Miss.
小姐
Another martini.
再来一杯马提尼
Oh, hell, no. I know she ain't talkin' to me.
哦,天啊,不.我知道她不是在跟我说话
Ashley, she doesn't work here.
艾希莉,她不是在这儿上班的
If she isn't here to work, then what is she here for?
如果她在这里不是上班,那是来干什么的?
Oh, hells no, Miss Thing. You best pump your brakes.
该死的不是,小姐东东,你最好闭上嘴巴
She's my ex-wife's sister.
她是我前妻的妹妹
I would have killed her myself years ago.
好几年前我就想亲手杀了她
It's Mrs. Arness!
亚妮丝夫人来了!
Mmm. Old Iron Ass be lookin' mean.
老家伙看起来很小气
Yes. You have to go.
是的,你必须得走了
You like raw oysters, Charlene?
你喜欢生吗,夏琳?
Yeah. I guess I can hang out for a bit.
好啊,我想我可以在这边多待一会
They got any hot wings around here?
这里有哈辣鸡翅吗?
All right. Whatever you want. Yes.
好的,你要什么都可以
- You give me a place to stay? - Yes.
你给我地方住? 行
- And you work on my case? - Around the clock.
你会帮我打官司? 完全可以
I'll leave when you expunge my record.
如果你帮我清除了犯罪记录 我马上就离开
Consider it expunged.
没问题
All right. I'd like a key, please.
好吧,请给我一个钥匙
Mr. Sanderson?
山德森先生?
Mrs. Arness.
亚妮丝夫人
Who is your associate?
你的同伴是谁?
This is Howie Rottman, the attorney I told you about.
这位是郝威罗特曼 就我跟你提过的那位律师
A great pleasure to meet you, Mrs. Arness.
很荣幸认识你,亚妮丝夫人
I meant her.
我是指她
Her?
她?
Her is... her...
她是...她...
She is our... our nanny.
她是我们的...她是我们的奶妈
Dad, I'm bored.
爸,好无聊
Kids, how good to see you.
孩子们,见到你们真好
Don't we just love our nanny, Charlene?
我们是不是很喜欢我们的奶妈夏琳啊?
Uh... Y-yeah.
唔...是的
Don't you just love being our nanny, Charlene?
你是不是很喜欢当我们的奶妈啊,夏琳?
Yessir.
是的,先生
Now I'm gonna go on down to the pool with the child'n.
现在我要跟孩子们去池子玩水了
Maybe we make fun of the white folks again, huh, kids?
也许我们再来捉弄白种人,孩子们
Oh, the kids just love her.
哦,孩子们就是爱她
- What a sense of humor. - Yeah.
真幽默 没错
Peter, I'm going to hang by the pool.
彼德,我要去池边逛逛
If you need me, that's where I'll be.
找我的话,我就在那里
Mrs. Arness.
亚妮丝夫人
Uh, right this way,
这边请,亚妮丝夫人
Come, William.
来吧,威廉
You have the papers?
你有带文件来吗?
Oh, yes, yes, I do.
是的,我有带
Strange clothes for a nanny.
奶妈穿那样子真奇怪
Well, it's a fashion to kids.
对孩子们而言很新潮
- Ow! - William, mind.
威廉,注意点
Hello, Sanderson family!
你好,山德森一家!
Georgey, don't forget poker night!
乔治,别忘了扑克之夜!
I won't.
不会忘的
How could I forget poker night?
我怎会忘记扑克之夜?
I propose a toast.
我想干一杯
Okay.
好的
To us.
敬我们俩
May we always...
愿我俩生生世世...
- Mmm. - Sorry. It's mine.
抱歉,是找我的
Oh, you're not gonna answer that, are you?
你不会去接吧?
Well, it might be... might be one of my kids.
可能是...我孩子打来的
Just one minute.
一下子就好
Sorry.
对不起
Hello?
喂?
Hey, it's me.
嘿,是我
Oh, hi, Ashley. Everything okay?
嗨,艾希莉,一切都还好吧?
I don't know.
我不知道
I saw Peter hanging out at the club today.
我今天在俱乐部里看到彼德
He was mingling with a large black woman.
他跟一个巨无霸黑妞在交往
What? What are you talking about?
什么? 你在说什么呀?
He said it was his nanny.
他说是他的奶妈
She didn't look like any nanny I'd ever seen.
跟我见过的奶妈样子一点都不像
She was all... tattooed and welfarish.
她整个人...又黑又胖
It was...
那是...
Oh, is that funny to you? Is that funny?
你认为很好笑吗? 很好笑吗?
Am I funny to you?
你觉得我好笑吗?
No, no. That's not funny.
不,不是的,那不好笑
Were you laughing at me?
你在笑我?
Oh, I wasn't...
哦,我不是...
Stop. Get away.
住手,走开啦
No, I wasn't laughing at you.
不,我不是在笑你
Just... hang on.
只是...等等
Um, you know, look, I know Peter. I know him.
你知道,听着,我了解彼德,我了解他
He's not gonna spend all his time taking care of the kids.
他不会花所有时间去照顾孩子
He went and hired somebody!
他会雇人来照顾!
Seriously, Kate! This woman was no nanny.
认真点,凯特! 这女人不是奶妈
You need to do something.
你必须采取点行动
I saw this woman. I was there.
我有看到这女人,我当时在那里
Shouldn't you at least be looking at references?
你至少不是该查明一下她的身份?
Thank you. Thank you.
谢谢,谢谢
Listen, Peter is nothing if not responsible.
听着,彼德若是逢场作戏就不要紧
It's not like he's gonna hire a convicted felon.
又不像是雇了个已定谳的重刑犯
Oh, I wouldn't be too sure about that.
哦,我可不敢那么肯定
Let's see... we got resisting arrest, assaulting an officer,
我们来瞧瞧...拒捕、袭警
repeated attempts at eye-gouging,
连续戳人眼珠
and... scrotum crushing.
以及...捣毁下体
Well, I was a little riled up, being framed and all.
被人诬陷,我当时有些气愤
And your clothes and I.D. Were found at the scene.
现场找到你的衣物和证件
All plants. I never robbed nobody!
全是栽赃的,我没抢任何人!
Okay.
好吧
I know my rights. I get an appeal.
我知道我的权利,我要上诉!
I get an appeal!
我要上诉!
You only get an appeal if you were convicted and incarcerated.
除非你被判刑入狱才能申请上诉
You were released.
你被释放了啊
Look, why don't you just start over?
听着,你何不重头来过?
Go back to school and get at least a passing familiarity
回学校去,至少先搞好...
With the English language.
...英语
It's no end to what you can accomplish
肯定前途无量
with a little commitment.
只需做点小小承诺
My daughter Sarah is fully committed,
我女儿莎拉完全允诺
and she's going places.
她就要功成名就
Oh, she's goin' places, all right.
哦,她要出去了,没错
So, it's a charitable remainder trust.
还剩一大笔信托财产
That way, the old tightwad gets a huge deduction every year.
看样子,这老守财奴每年会得到一笔 为数可观的减免额
Uh, no more calls, Sofia.
不接任何电话,苏菲亚
It's not a call. There's someone here...
不是电话,是有人来...
Girl, get out!
小姐,出去!
I do not know who you are...
我不知道你是谁...
Send her in.
让她进来
Bet you know me now, huh?
现在你知道我是谁了吧?
This couldn't wait until tonight?
不能等今晚再说吗?
Come in, have a seat, spend some time.
进来,请坐一会吧
Thanks, homeboy, and, no, it can't wait.
谢了,不行,不能等了
You gotta check this out.
你得看看这个
- What is it? - I found the deposition.
是什么? 我找到这份笔录
The prosecution interviewed an eyewitness,
警察当局访问过一位目击证人
and she told them that the perpetrator
她告诉警方说犯人...
didn't have a tattoo on the chest.
胸口没有刺青
They never told my lawyer about this shit.
警方却没有告诉我的律师这点
That's withholding exculp...
那样是隐匿申明...
Exculpatory evidence. People vs. Stanley, I know.
申明无罪的证据,"法律对话",我晓得
How do you know that?
你怎么知道的呢?
Why wouldn't she know that? She's got it goin' on.
她怎会不知道? 她说的头头是道
Damn, Pete, all I did in there was read law books.
该死,彼德,我被关在里头 可了不少法律书籍
And with comprehension.
而且滚瓜烂熟
Made you think I was a lawyer.
让你误认为我是律师
I mean, you obviously have pockets of intelligence.
我意思是,你显然聪慧过人
So, why do you walk and talk and act the way you do?
为何你走路讲话和行为举止这样?
Because it's sexy.
因为很性感
It ain't actin'!
我没做作!
This is who I am.
我就是这样
I mean, you think I can't talk like you?
我是说,你以为我无法像你们 那种讲话方式吗?
Oh, Peter,
哦,彼德
I absolutely love what you've done with the place!
我非常喜欢你这间的摆设装璜!
It's so sterile, so... so bland, so wonderful!
好干净,好...好舒适,好棒!
See? You can do it.
你瞧? 你行的
Oh, you like that, huh?
你喜欢那样是吧?
Well, you can kiss my natural black ass,
你有权不喜欢黑人
because I don't need your approval.
因为我不需要你的认同
No, she don't need
不,她不需要你的认同
Hey, you don't think I compromise the way I act?
嘿,你不会以为我会这样妥协了吧?
You think I like walking around like an uptight... honky?
你以为我喜欢像个发怒的白人走来走去?
Yes. I know your lingo.
是的,我知道你一定莫名其妙
Peter, Mr. Tobias is coming to see you.
彼德,托拜尔斯先生要来见你
Oh, God.
哦,天哪
Well, this should be interesting.
这应该会很有趣
Uh-oh. What we gotta do, play "hide the sister"?
我们怎么办,玩"藏姐姐"游戏?
Or do I gotta do that slave thing again?
还是再来玩奴隶游戏呢?
Just... just act natural.
只要....表现自然点
- Let's get her out of here. - Why don't we get her out?
我们送她出去吧 有何不可呢?
Peter... Howie.
彼德...郝威
Ed.
艾德
Who is this?
这位是谁?
- Uh, this is the... - Well, we were just having...
这位是... 我们只是在...
Well, Mr. Sanderson, I can see you are very busy.
山德森先生,我看得出你很忙
That's why I really appreciate you
所以我真的很感激你
offering your services free of charge.
提供免费服务
Oh, I... well, I just... gosh.
哦,我...我只是...天哪
Peter...
彼德...
She is...
她是...
Well, see, Mr. Sanderson here,
你瞧,这儿的山德森先生
being the heavenly man that he is...
真是个天大好人...
God bless you!
愿神保佑你!
Oh, you got that anointing on you...
你已受到祈福了
...has offered to do the taxes for the Compton Evangelistic
替康普顿教会办理税务
Episcopal Baptist church of South Central.
中南部浸信会
You know, just anything to help
你知道的,略尽微薄之力
Reverend Shack... tillfont.
雪克牧师
Just call him Shack.
叫他雪克就好
Shack.
雪克
Well, I'll let you guys go.
我让你们去忙吧
I'll see you at choir rehearsal on Thursday.
周四唱诗班排演时见了
7:00, now!
七点,好的!
I'll escort Mrs. Shacktill... font
我陪雪克夫人...
to the elevator.
去搭电梯
Gentlemen.
各位
Uh, Peter, we're really in a crunch.
彼德,我们财务真的有危机
I just got word that another firm's in the running
我刚收到消息,有别间公司可能获得
for the R&S account.
R&S公司财源
We need to close this deal.
我们必须完成这笔交易
Look...
听着...
I have no problem being Peter's wingman on this one.
这案子我可以协助彼德
Oh, well, thanks anyway, but I really have it under control,
总之,谢啦,不过我真的大局在握
so, you don't have to worry about a thing, Ed.
所以你根本不用担心,艾德
Good. Then I'll expect you to wrap it up in a day or two.
很好,那我希望你一两天之内解决完毕
That's the plan, certainly.
那是计划,当然
Could you...
你能不能...
- Sure. - Thank you.
当然 谢谢
She can't tee up her own ball?
她自己不会摆球吗?
I've been playing this game for many years...
我玩这运动已经好多年了
That's what it feels like.
看样子是没错
...and it's all about patience.
全是为了培养耐心
Well, you beat me by 19.
你打赢我19次了
MRS. ARNESS: Uh, let's make it 20.
那就凑个20次吧
All right.
好的
Mrs. Arness, I was wondering
亚妮丝夫人,不知道...
if you'd like to come over to my house on Thursday
你是否愿意周四过来我家
and possibly look over the contract.
先看一遍合约内容
I'll have to check with my secretary, Julia.
我得和我秘书茱莉亚查一下行程
Mrs. Arness, would you excuse me for a minute?
亚妮丝夫人,能否失陪个几分钟?
I just have to check on my children.
我得去看看我的孩子一下
Oh, of course. You do that.
哦,当然,去吧
I'd like to dip you in Cheez Whiz
我想把你沾一下起司酱
and spread you over a Ritz Cracker,
涂抹在丽滋饼干上
if I'm not being too subtle.
如果我不是过于难以捉摸
Boy, you are some kind of freaky.
小子,你真是有点古怪
Oh, you have no idea.
哦,你不知道
You got me straight trippin', boo.
你教我神魂颠倒
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, what are you doing here?
嘿嘿嘿! 嘿,你在这里做什么?
What does it look like? I'm on a date.
你说像什么呢? 我在约会
On a date.
约会
She's on a date? She's a felon.
她在约会? 她可是重刑犯
- I am not a felon. - Hey, what is she doing here?
我才不是重刑犯 嘿,她来这里做什么?
Get used to it, Twiggy.
习惯吧,瘦皮猴
You're gonna be seeing a lot more of me around here.
你会常常在这里见到我的
Not without a broom in your hand.
手上还拿了把扫帚
If I have, it's 'cause I'm here to sweep up the white trash.
要是有拿,是因为我要扫白种垃圾
Save it for the YMCA, Jemima.
留着去跟女青年会说吧,肉饼脸
Bitch! I'm gonna kick the bulimia out of your ass!
婊子! 我要揍得你哭爹喊娘的!
Have you ever had a tempered moment?
你就不能心平气和一下吗?
Why don't you go back to the vodka bottle you crawled out of?
你何不回去好好喝你的酒呢?
Mrs. Arness is here.
亚妮丝夫人来了
I am sheltering you. I'm helping you.
我在保护你,我在帮你
Remember, I helped you...
记住,我帮你...
All right! I'll let it ride.
好啦! 我不会跟她计较的
Thank you for letting it ride. That is wise and mature.
感谢你大人有大量,既聪明又成熟
Now, just get her walking that way.
现在,带她从那边走
Let me show you the place, Charlene.
让我带你四处逛逛,夏琳
Looking good, Lois!
气色不错哦,洛伊斯!
Hey, freak boy...
嘿,怪小子...
I'm gonna make myself a little more luscious for you, okay?
我要为你打扮得更加娇艳动人,好吗?
I'll be right back.
我马上回来
Okay, precious.
好的,太棒了
What are you doin' in here?
你进来做什么?
I told you you was gonna be seein' more of me, right?
我说过你会不时看到我,对吧?
Look, I came here to warn you.
听着,我来警告你
You keep disrespecting me,
你再对我无礼的话
and it's gonna get rough around here.
这里就会天下大乱
Back off, Shaniqua.
退后,黑鬼
You don't scare me.
你吓唬不了我
You know what? That's it.
你知道怎么吗? 没错
You must need a little more eye shadow, right? Come on!
你一定想多擦点眼影,对吧? 来呀!
You've messed with the wrong W.A.S.P., bitch.
你惹错对象了,婊子
Compliments of Tae-Bo,
有氧拳击健身操
two hours a day, five days a week.
一天练两小时,一星期五天
Compliments of the 'hood, 24 hours a day, all my life.
吃屎吧! 一天廿四小时,我练了一辈子
You know, for a skinny white ho, you're pretty tough.
你知道,对个瘦巴巴的白种婊子而言 你算相当厉害了
And I don't ever want to have this conversation again!
我不想再多费唇舌了
"The girl had dou..."
"这女孩有着一..."
"...ble..."
"...对..."
"...double D-cups."
"一对Ｄ罩杯"
There you go. You got it, lil' man.
好了,你懂了,小鬼
"I put my mouth on her nip..."
"我把嘴巴放在她的奶..."
"...ples."
"...子上"
What is that?
那是什么?
What are you doing letting him read th...
你怎么能让他看这...
He read. You read.
他看过,你看过
Georgey, you read.
乔治,你看过
I'm gonna kill you!
我要宰了你!
I am so proud of you.
我真以你为傲
I'm turning you in!
我要送你回牢里去!
Pfft. I found it in your drawer.
我在你抽屉找到的
Well, I am a grown man of 54... 41... 49 years old,
我是个大人了,54...41...49岁了
and he's 8, and what I read in the privacy of my...
他才8岁,我看的都是偷偷摸摸地...
How'd you do it?
你怎么弄的?
Oh, God, I'm never gonna get this done.
哦,老天,老是弄不完
Look, the boy don't look carefully
听着,这小子没有仔细看
at the details in a word,
字里头的涵义
so most of the time, he's just guessin'.
所以大部份时间他只是在猜测
What you got to do is just slow it down
你所要做的便是冷静下来
and give him somethin' stimulatin' to read.
给他一些激励的书看
Dad?
爸?
What's a rack?
什么是rack?
It's a country.
是个国家
I was just doin' it 'cause he was botherin' me.
他一直烦我,我才那么做的
Well, either way...
要不然...
Can you get rid of this?
帮我丢掉好吗?
Just put it back in my room,
好了,放回我房间
'cause I'll get rid of it, 'cause I have a special...
我会丢是因为我有特别的...
Well, Mrs. Kline, how wonderful to see you.
克莱恩夫人,见到你太好了
Come in!
进来!
It's girls poker night at the house.
今晚是女子扑克之夜要在你家
Where's my little dealer?
我的小庄家呢?
Well, just wait right here, and I will just go get him.
请在此等一下,我去叫他
Georgey, Mrs. Kline is here!
乔治,克莱恩夫人来了!
Hi, Mrs. Kline.
嗨,克莱恩夫人
Come on, Georgey!
来吧,乔治!
Tonight, I'm gonna teach you to bluff.
今晚我要教你如何虚张声势
And I think we need to comb your hair differently.
我想该替你梳个不同发型
You look like a fag.
你好像同性恋者
- I'm not a fag! - I didn't say you were.
我不是同性恋者! 我没说你是
- Hello. - Hi. How are you?
你好 嗨,你好吗?
Oh, good evening, sir.
晚安,先生
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
等等,等等
Dad, I don't want you to freak out, okay?
爸,我不想教你抓狂,好吗?
Why would I freak out?
我干嘛抓狂?
Dad, this is Aaron.
爸,这是亚伦
Hi.
嗨
- Hello. - How do you do, sir?
你好 你好,先生
I-I-I'm so glad to actually meet you.
我...我...很高兴终于见到你了
I-I-I told Sarah that it was very important
我...我...告诉莎拉那非常重要
that you feel comfortable with me
你能对我感到放心
taking her to my parents' for dinner.
让我带她去和我父母一块吃顿晚餐
So, this is a date?
那这算是约会?
Oh, um, I'll have her home by 11:00 at the latest, sir?
最迟晚上11点我会送她回家,先生
I guess that'd be all right.
我想应该没问题吧
All right. Did it work?
好了,有效吧?
Yeah, like a charm, my friend.
对,神奇妙方,朋友
All right. Let's party.
好了,狂欢吧
Hey, watch the seats.
嘿,小心座位
- All right... - Oh, shut up.
好了... 哦,闭嘴
No, I'm serious. It's leather.
不,我说真的,那是真皮的
Well, look at you, all growed up.
看看你,完全成熟了
There's nothing to eat in the house.
屋子里没吃的
Yeah. You comin' to a point?
对,说重点吧
Well, I'm hungry. Are you?
我饿了,你饿不饿?
You askin' me out?
你是在约我出去吗?
Well, no, I'm not.
不,不是
Yes, I am.
是的,没错
Okay.
好的
Oh, look at the legs on this wine.
哦,看看这杯脚
I'm telling you, this place is bangin'.
我告诉你,这地方太帕
Don't you just mean, "This is nice"?
你刚是不是说"这里很棒"?
Why the word "bangin"' make you so uptight?
为何""这个字让你这么紧张?
You're smart... if you'd just deign to speak English
你很聪明,只要你肯屈就一下讲英语
with what you learned on the Internet and in prison,
利用你在网路上及牢里所学到的知识
you could be a paralegal tomorrow.
他日一定能成为律师助理
Like they gonna be beatin' down my door to let me in school.
好比要让我去上学得先撞破我的门再说
You're exactly the kind of person they want.
你绝对是符合他们需求的人选
Well, why would I want to do that, anyway?
总之,为何我要那么做?
I've been to your office.
我去过你的办公室
Everybody's all uptight, overworked,
人人精神紧绷、工作过量
tired, stressed-out, don't see their family.
疲劳不堪、压力过重、见不到家人
"Ooh, Ed is comin'." "Ooh, Tobias."
"哦,艾德来了!" "哦,托拜尔斯!"
I get a wedgie just walking in your office.
我大大方方走进你的办公室
Hey, it's what people do. They work.
嘿,人就是这样子,工作嘛
Look, all I'm sayin' is I did the confinement thing
听着,我要说的是我做这种禁锢的事
for four years.
长达四年之久
If you're so concerned with my future,
如果你那么关心我的未来
just help me clear my name.
就帮我洗刷污名
I got it from there.
我从那里体会到的
I got my own dreams, my own goals.
我有我自己的梦想、自己的目标
Hey, give it to me.
嘿,给我
Hey! What'd you do that for?!
嘿! 你干嘛那样做?!
- 'Cause you work too much. - This is my phone!
因为你工作过度 这是我的手机!
That's probably why your wife left your sorry ass.
你老婆可能就是那样才离开你的
Okay, Oprah, if you're so good at relationships,
好的,欧普拉,如果你对人际关系那么行
how come you don't have a boyfriend?
你怎么没有交男朋友?
I had one.
我交过一个
It's just I haven't seen or heard from him
只是我很久没见到他或听到他的消息了
since I went in four years ago.
自从四年前入狱之后
Were you in love with him?
你爱他吗?
Come on, let's go dance.
来吧,我们去跳舞
Ha ha ha ha... no.
哈哈哈哈...不
Come on. When is the last time you danced?
快啦,你上次跳舞是什么时候?
At my wedding.
在我的婚礼
Don't worry, I can dance. It's just that I don't wanna.
别担心,我会跳,只是我不想跳
Come on, smooth. Show me what you're workin' with.
快点,让我看看你有多行
I can dance. I just don't want to dance.
我会跳,只是我不想跳
Man, you can't dance.
你根本不会跳
- Well, I got moves. - Let me see.
我会跳 那让我见识一下
All right, all right.
好吧,好吧
Okay, one last little drink here.
好,再喝最后一小杯
What, you got to pee?
怎么,你想尿尿?
This was big in high school.
这招在我高中时很流行
Man, look, you can't dance from your brain.
天啊,听着,你不能用脑子去跳舞
You gotta feel it. Now, come on.
你得去感受音乐,好了,来吧
Show me how you made them kids.
我教你怎样跳才对
- What the hell... - How's this?
搞什么... 这招如何?
That's great for an epileptic. Come on, now.
好像羊癫疯发作似的,来吧
You gotta move your pelvis with it.
你屁股要这样子摆动
More hips. There you go.
屁股多摇点,行了
Get smooth with it.
动作轻柔点
Well, I'm sorry. I can't help it. I miss him.
对不起,我忍不住,我真的很想他
Oh, snap out of it, already.
哦,快点恢复正常吧
I'm snapped. I'm snappy.
我没事了,我很好
Oh, God, Ash.
哦,天哪,艾希莉
I still can't believe you were hit by a car.
我还是不相信你被车子撞到
Did you call a lawyer?
你有打电话叫律师吗?
Oh, I can't talk to a lawyer. I was jaywalking.
哦,我不能打给律师,我闯越马路
So, can we just stop...
我们能否别再...
- What? - Oh, my God.
怎么? 哦,我的天啊
What?
怎么了?
Look at that!
看看那边!
Oh, my God, it's true. Look at that! Look at that!
哦,天哪,是真的 看看那! 看看那!
He never danced like that with me.
他从没跟我那样子跳过舞
I'm gonna go talk to him.
我要去找他
No! Sit!
不! 坐下!
Why?
为什么?
I can't tell you.
我不能告诉你
If I talk about it,
要是我说了
gangster people will come to my house and cut me.
帮派份子会到我家杀了我
Oh, he almost looks like a fun person.
他看起来很开心
Must've been me.
一定是我的关系
Was it me?
是我吗?
No. Stop beating yourself up. It's him.
不,别再自责了,是他的错
Can we just get out of here? Now?
我们离开这里好吗? 马上?
You know what they say...
你知道俗话说...
once you go black, you never go back.
一入不归路,便无法回头
Can we get the check, please?
我们买单好吗?
And that's why I worked so hard,
所以我才那么拼命工作
so I could give Kate a good life, then it backfired!
好给凯特一个美好的生活 然而却弄巧成拙!
Man, bitches don't care nothin' about that shit.
天哪,女人才不会在乎那点
Oh, bitches do too care.
哦,女人非常在乎的
I'm gonna tell you a secret...
我要告诉你一个秘密
sometimes I drive by our old house, and I just look at it,
有时我开车经过我们旧家 我只是看一眼
and I just remember our life, and it just hurts!
就忆起我们的生活,太令人伤心了!
Man, that is so pathetic, P. Diddy.
天啊,那真是太惨了,吹牛老爹
But you know what? I'm gonna help you get her back.
但你知道怎么吗? 我要帮你挽回她
How?
怎么挽回?
Well, first, we gotta create a mood.
首先,我们要营造出一种气氛
Just like at the restaurant, baby.
就像在餐厅一样,宝贝
I'm already there.
我已经在了
Yeah. Now, feel the Barry.
对! 现在,体会一下巴瑞
Feel Barry White. Talk like Barry.
体会一下巴瑞怀特,口气像巴瑞
- Okay, that's Barry. - Yeah.
好的,那是巴瑞 好耶
This is Kate.
这是凯特
Hey, Kate. Yeah.
嘿,凯特 对
I want you to talk nasty to her!
我要你对她满口淫秽字眼
Talk nasty!
满口淫秽!
I'd like to kiss you a lot.
我想吻你千百遍
Cut that sensitive shit, Nancy Boy!
别说那种感性的话,娘娘腔的!
What?
什么?
- You gotta be a beast! - A beast!
你要当个野兽! 野兽!
Yeah!
对!
In the bedroom, a woman wants a man
卧室里,女人需要男人
that knows how to ride her when she bucks.
懂得如何驾驭她顽强的抵抗
Ride 'em when she bucks! Ride 'em!
霸王硬上弓! 上弓!
It's just... I can't. It's a sculpture. I just can't.
只是...我不行 那是雕塑品,我办不到
All right, okay.
好的,好吧
Use me, then.
那用我示范吧
Huh?
什么?
Damn it, grab these.
该死,抓这里
- What?! - Grab 'em!
什么?! 抓呀!
Oh, I get it, yeah.
哦,我懂了,对
- Hey, Kate. - Uh-huh.
嘿,凯特
Yeah, you've been waitin' for this for a while, huh?
你一直在等这一刻好一阵子了,是吧?
That's right. Now, what you gonna do to her?
没错! 现在你要怎么对她?
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do!
我会让你明白我要做什么!
I'm gonna give you an aromatherapy massage
我要帮你做芳香按摩
with incense!
香薰疗法!
No! Come on, now!
不! 来吧,快!
Wimps give aromatherapy massages!
胆小鬼才做芳香按摩!
Tell her again!
再告诉她一遍!
All right!
好了!
I'm gonna have...
我要...
sexual intercourse, baby!
性交,宝贝!
No, you... you a beast! You need some of these.
不,你...你这只禽兽! 你需要点这些
- Yeah. - Cojones grande!
对! 大睾丸!
Yeah! I'm gonna put 'em in my pants!
对! 我要塞进我的裤子里!
- Get in there, boys! - Now, grab 'em!
进去,小子! 现在抓着蛋蛋!
- Grab 'em. Yeah, hey, baby! - Grab 'em!
抓着,对,嘿,宝贝! 抓着!
Now, what you gonna do? What you gonna do?!
好了,你想干嘛? 你想干嘛?!
Yeah, Mama! You gonna be my tawdry little woman?
耶,妈妈! 你要当我的押寨夫人吗?
Damn right! Now get to humpin'!
他妈的没错! 现在扑上来吧!
- How 'bout that, huh?! - Yeah!
那样如何啊?! 好耶!
How would you like me to pounce on you
喜欢我扑向你吗?
- like a lion from above? - I like it! I like it!
像头猛狮从上头扑过去 喜欢! 我喜欢!
- Yo! - That's what I'm talkin'!
那正是我所说的!
You ain't just no king of the jungle,
你不只是丛林之王
you own that jungle!
你拥有整片丛林!
That's your pride!
那是你的骄傲!
You own that jungle, and ain't no one
你拥有丛林,没有人...
gonna come around and mess with your pride!
敢在太岁爷头上动土!
That's right! I like that.
没错! 我喜欢那样
Yeah! You ain't ready for that shit! Come on, now!
耶! 你还没准备好嘿咻呢! 来吧!
Be a beast! What you gonna do when she starts ridin', huh?
兽性大发! 当她开始在上头骑时 你要怎么办?
Take care of her! That's what I'm gonna do!
好好"照顾"她! 我就要那么做!
- Uh-huh! Uh-huh! - You're mine, Kate!
你是我的了,凯特!
- Ride that lighting rod! - You don't need these no more.
快马策鞭! 你不再需要这些了
You got your own! You found your balls!
你自己就有! 你找到你的蛋蛋了!
Yeah, I don't need those balls! I got my own balls!
对,我不需要那些了! 我自己就有蛋蛋!
Mandingo!
我的妈呀!
What goes on in your personal life is none of our business,
你的私生活怎样我们管不着
but if it begins to affect the firm,
但如果开始影响到公司
we need to call attention to it.
我们就得关注了
Guys, we were moving a statue,
各位,我们在搬一尊雕像
and we lost our footing, and we fell.
脚步踩空了,所以才倒在一块
My sister's under the impression
我姐姐看到的是...
that you were humping your nanny.
当时你正在搞你的奶妈
I was not humping my nanny!
我没有在搞我的奶妈!
Peter, surely you understand that if Mrs. Arness
彼德,你一定明白,如果亚妮丝夫人
were to suspect any instability on your part...
怀疑你不安于室...
There is no instability in my home.
我没有不安于室
You sure you can trust this guy?
你确定你信得过这家伙吗?
Well, hey, he's helping me reopen my case.
嘿,他在帮我重审我的案子
Y'all got any leads?
有任何线索吗?
Well, a still from the bank surveillance camera
银行监视器有拍到一个画面
is on its way here,
正要送过来这里
and we found a deposition that could help.
我们找到一份有用的笔录
Well, that's cool, baby.
那太好了,宝贝
If there's anything I can do to help,
如果有什么我可以帮上忙的
anything... you just holler.
任何事都行...你只要说一声即可
I gotta run.
我得走了
Hey, Widow, if you meant what you just said,
威多,你刚刚说的话是不是真心的
it's not gonna be an easy job.
那不是件易事
I know it ain't.
我知道不是
I just gotta know that if things get rough,
我只是得知道万一事情变糟了
you're not gonna run out on me.
你不会弃我而去
I've been waitin' four years for this.
我一直等这一刻等了四年
I ain't gonna mess up.
我不会乱来的
Planning another heist?
计划再抢一次?
No. Why would you say that?
不,为什么你会那么说?
I don't know.
不知道
Maybe it was hearing the words "job" and "hot"
也许是听到"工作"和"棘手"这几个字
bandied between two tattooed people?
出现在两个黑人对话中吧?
That was just my old boyfriend I told you about... Widow.
那人只是我的旧男友 我告诉过你关于...威多的事
He's just tryin' to get back with me.
他只是想重回我怀抱
I'm tellin' you the truth!
我在告诉你实情!
Look, I just didn't want you to see him,
听着,我是不希望你见他
because Widow, he ain't been the best boyfriend,
因为威多他一直不是个好男友
and I knew he'd be all over me.
而且我晓得他会一直缠着我
Now you suddenly care what I think?
怎么现在突然关心起我的想法了?
No.
不是
Maybe.
也许
A little bit.
有一点点
No more late visits?
别再有访客了好吗?
Word.
我对天发誓
Convicted felon's honor?
以定谳罪犯的荣耀吗?
Innocent convicted felon's honor.
无辜入狱的罪犯的荣耀
Now, give me some dap, right there on the edge.
好了,来击个拳,拳对拳
Right there, and then come up here like that.
先那样,然后再像那样往上
Pow, like that.
就像那样子
Hello?
喂?
Dad!
爸!
Hey, sweetie.
嘿,甜心
Is Charlene there?
夏琳在吗?
Yeah, she's here. Do you want to talk to her?
她在,你要和她讲话?
- You okay? - Yeah, I'm...
你还好吧? 是的,我...
All right.
好吧
- Sarah? Okay. - Girl talk.
莎拉? 好的 女孩子的悄悄话
What up, dog?
怎么了,孩子?
I need you to come pick me up. I can't talk about it right now.
我需要你来接我回家,我现在不方便谈
Where you at?
你在哪里?
I'm on the corner of Venice and Canal,
在转角那间"威尼斯运河"
and there's a whole lot of people out front.
前门外面有一大堆人
- Please don't tell my dad! - All right.
拜托别告诉我爸! 好的
No, just calm down. I'm comin' to get you.
不会的,冷静点,我马上去接你
I'm sorry. I didn't know who else to call.
对不起,我不知道还有谁可找
It's cool. What's goin' on?
没关系,怎么回事?
Hey, Sarah, what have you been up to? Hee hee!
嘿,莎拉,你怎么样?
Is that your boyfriend?
那是你男朋友吗?
No, he's not my boyfriend.
不,他不是我男朋友
I liked his friend, Mike,
我喜欢他的朋友麦克
and we hung out a few times, and he was always really nice,
我们出去过几次,他一直对我很好
but then... all he wanted to do tonight was have sex,
可是后来...今晚他只想上床
I mean, he moved in kind of rough, and...
我是说他举止有点粗暴,而且...
He got rough with you? Where he at?
他对你施暴? 他人在哪?
He went back there with that group.
和那票人回那里去了
Go wait downstairs.
下楼等我
Yo, Mike!
麦克!
Please, don't kill me!
拜托别杀我!
Oh, God!
哦,天哪!
What are you? Crazy?!
你是谁? 疯子吗?!
Pull me up! What do you want?!
拉我上去! 你想干嘛?!
Sarah!
莎拉!
Mike has somethin' to say to you.
麦克有话对你说
Say "sorry"!
说"对不起"!
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry! God, I am sorry!
对不起! 说"对不起"! 老天,对不起!
Say "No means no."
说"不就表示不"
No means no!
不就表示不!
She was where?!
她在哪?!
Calm down. It's just...
冷静点,只是...
- She is 14! - She's 15! Wait!
她才14岁! 她15岁了! 等等!
G... well... oh!
嗯...哦!
Look...
听着...
Sarah don't need a warden.
莎拉不需要守卫
She needs her father... you...
她需要的是她父亲 你...
so you can't get mad, all right?
所以你不能生气,好吗?
You do it, she'll never tell you anything again.
你一生气,她就不会再告诉你任何事了
All right. I get it. I get it.
好的,我懂,我懂了
Just be cool. Just play it cool, you know what I mean?
冷静点,有话好好说,你知道我的意思吧?
Just listen to her. Let her do the talkin'.
倾听她说话,让她自己说出来
I am listening to you!
我全听你的啦!
Thank you.
谢谢
Don't trip.
别动怒
So...
那么...
you went out with a boy...
你跟个男孩子出去...
and he took you to a party,
他带你去舞会
where kids were... drinking
一堆孩子在...喝酒
and "trippin' on E."...
神智恍惚...
and then he took you up to a room
然后他带你上楼到房间里
where he tried to...
他打算...
"get all up in that..."
来硬的...
which he... didn't?
他...有没有?
And then Charlene came...
接着夏琳赶来...
in my new car... and brought you home
驾着我的新车载你回家
after first... "bitchslapping" him.
在这之前先...痛扁他一顿
...that was some night.
今晚太爽了
Oh, Dad!
哦,老爸!
I can't believe you're not killing me!
不敢相信你竟然没宰了我!
Oh! This is so great! I want everything out in the open!
哦! 这太棒了! 我要把一切通通坦白告诉你
Oh, I have so much more to tell you!
哦,我有好多话想告诉你!
Kate, what are you doing here?
凯特,你在这里干嘛?
W-What are you doing here?
你来这里做什么?
It's my shortcut home from work.
我下班抄捷径回家
No, it's not.
才不是呢
- Yes, it is. - Is not.
是 不是
I thought you were in the mountains.
我以为你在山上
Well, yeah, I-I came back early.
是没错,我提前回来了
There were bears that were mauling the campers
有熊袭击露营者
and eating them.
还吃掉他们
Wow.
哇
But other than that... nothing went wrong with your...
话说回来...有出事吗? 你的...
Oh, no, no. He's great.
哦,不,不,他很好
Yeah, I liked him.
对,我喜欢他
So, how's your...
那你的...
My what?
我的什么?
Your life?
你的生活?
Anything hip and new?
有什么新奇的吗?
No.
没有
I'm having a good time with the kids.
我和孩子们在一起很开心
Good. Glad you're having fun with her.
很好,很高兴你和她在一起很开心
Them.
他们
What?
怎么?
You look, um...
你瞧...
Yeah.
是的
Rested.
轻松自在
Nice. You look nice.
很好,你看起来挺好
So, um, I guess I'll come by later and pick up the kids.
那么,我想我晚些时候会来接走孩子们
Oh, I was wondering if I could keep them through Friday.
哦,我想知道我是否能留他们过星期五
Really? You're not too busy?
真的?你不忙吗?
No.
不
Well, yes, it's okay.
好吧,就这么定了
It's wonderful, Peter.
太棒了,彼德
You know, if you wanted to come ov...
如果你想来...
Go ahead.
继续
Sorry.
对不起
Hello?
喂?
Yo, get your butt home, dog.
快给我滚回来
I will be home in my own sweet time, girlfriend.
我会在我自己的最美时刻回家的,女友
You gotta come now. Arness said she on her way over here.
你必须现在就动身 亚妮丝说她正在来这的路上
Oh, I forgot all about that.
哦,我把那些统统忘了
Oh, I'm sorry. I-I have to go.
哦,对不起,我不得不走了
I just forgot about something,
我把些事儿给忘了
but I want to continue this conversation,
但我想继续这个谈话
so I will call you, or you can call me on my cell.
所以我会给你打电话,或者你打电话给我
Bye!
再见!
Uh-huh.
嗯
- Is she here yet? - No!
她来了没? 没有!
The place is a mess!
这地方太乱了!
e gotta clean this place up!
我们必须把这儿打扫干净!
Hey, get upstairs and get ready!
嗨,上楼去做好准备!
And what are you reading?!
你在看什么?!
Get up there! Go! Go! Go! Go! Go!
起来!走!走!
Hey, yo, P., while we got this minute...
嘿,我们刚好有时间
there's somethin' I really been meanin' to tell you...
我有些事想告诉你
Well, you'll have to wait.
好吧,你等等
Kids! She's here!
孩子们!她在这儿!
Mrs. Arness?
亚妮丝夫人?
Oh!
哦!
I'll get right to the point, Mr. Sanderson.
我有些话要直说,山德森先生
There are rumors circulating
有流言在传说
that your personal life and your home are in disarray,
你的私人生活和你的家庭处于混乱
and this makes me feel very unsettled.
这让我觉得很忧虑
I don't know who misinformed you, but please, come in.
我不知道是谁误导了你,但是请进
I'd hate to think you're under any misapprehension
我不喜欢你被任何关于我和我家的谣传
about me or my family.
所误导
Sarah? Georgey?
莎拉? 乔治?
You remember Mrs. Arness?
你们还记得亚妮丝夫人吗?
So lovely to see you again.
再次见到你真是太高兴了
Um, Father, when you have a moment,
嗯,爸爸,如果你有时间
would you mind helping me with my report on Queen Victoria?
愿意帮我完成关于维多利亚女王的作业吗?
Sure, kitten.
没问题,亲爱的
And don't forget, Pop, tomorrow you have to come to school
还有别忘了,爸爸,明天你要到学校
and help hand out the food to the poor kids.
帮着分发食品给贫困孩子
Have I ever forgotten to help the poor kids?
我曾忘了帮助那些贫困孩子吗?
No, Pop. Never.
从来没有,爸爸
In truth, Mr. Sanderson, you have a lovely home.
说实话,山德森先生,你有个可爱的家
Thank you.
谢谢
And your children are very well-behaved.
你的孩子举止十分的好
They're angels.
他们是天使
Oh, William.
哦,威廉
Oh, look!
瞧啊!
He's even taken a fancy to your boy.
它喜欢你儿子
That's so sweet.
那太甜蜜了
Anyway, we can go to the den and get the contracts...
总之,我们到书房里谈谈契约...
What is that heavenly smell?
那么美味的味道是什么?
Ah, that would be Charlene preparing dinner.
啊,那是夏琳在准备饭菜
Anyway, the contracts...
总之,契约...
I haven't smelled home cooking like that since I was a child.
自打小时候起我就再没闻过家常菜的味道
Really? Anyway...
真的吗?但是...
Brings back such happy memories.
唤回了美好的回忆
Does it? Anyway, actually, the den is closer...
是吗?可是,事实上,书房...
Your table looks so inviting.
你的桌子看起来不错
Yes. It's too bad it's so small.
是的,可惜太小了
Small?
太小?
Well, actually, it's big, isn't it?
实际上,蛮大的,不是吗?
It's a big table, so...
是张大桌子,那么...
there would be room for one more.
能再容得下一个人
Oh, well, if it's not an imposition...
哦,如果不勉强的话...
Oh... oh.
哦...哦
Well, let me just go check if there's enough food.
好吧,我去看看食物是否足够
I'm not... I'm not sure,
我不能肯定
because, uh, actually, this is the night of, uh,
因为,实际上,今晚,嗯
Yiminum, the, uh... the holiday where
你知道的,今晚是特别节日
white people eat very little portions
白人要吃很少量的食物
because that was the night the Lord came down,
因为上帝就是在这个晚上下凡的
and he was given food,
他获赠了许多事物
and there was just too much, and he said, "No."
太多太多了,可他说“不用了”
And so, he had a smaller portion,
因此,他就吃了一小点
and that's why we might not have enough.
那就是为什么我们不能多准备的原因
So, I'll just go check on, uh, what the Lord would say.
那么,我就要去查查看上帝会说些什么
Just one second.
就一会儿
Come here, William.
过来,威廉
Hey, come here. Are you hungry?
嗨,过来,你饿了吗?
Charlene...
夏琳...
If there was ever a time I needed a favor, it's now.
如果有时间,我需要帮助,就现在
You got it, baby. Anything.
可以啊,亲爱的 随便
Oh, thank you!
哦,谢谢!
Oh. Mrs. Arness?
哦,亚妮丝夫人?
Yes? Oh, yes.
啊?
My family and I are pleased to invite you for dinner.
我和我全家很高兴邀请你来聚餐
Yeah, oh.
哦
Well, very well. I wasn't expecting this.
好啊,太好了 真的不必客气
Uh, but if you insist.
嗯,但如果你们坚持的话
And then afterwards, we can sign the contracts.
然后,我们就能签那份契约
Of course.
当然
Dinner is served.
饭好了
I was raised in the South, you know.
我是在南部长大的
That smells just like our Ivy's jambalaya.
那味道就像是我们长春藤的什锦菜肴
She was so wonderful.
她是那么的出色
We paid her nothing, of course, you know.
我们没付她工钱,当然的,你知道的
But, then, people had standards of service in those days.
但是,那时,人们有服务标准
And, of course, Ivy did know
当然,长春藤是知道的
that you serve from the left and collect from the right.
你从左边服务并从右边收集
Don't...
不要...
stop at that story, because I love hearing about your past.
别再说下去了,因我很喜欢听听你的过去
That is fascinating.
多迷人的啊
Oh, yes.
是啊
Well, anyway, as I was saying...
好吧,我是说...
Yeah.
是的
Yeah. Fast-actin'.
没错,快速起效剂
Fast-actin'.
快速起效剂
Ooh, I'm gonna get you.
哦,我要让你尝尝
I'm gonna get you.
让你尝尝
Uh-huh. I'll serve your food right.
我会在你的右边为你提供食物服务
Was it the left? Was it the right?
是左边?是右边?
Father's work with the Pasadena Republican Youth Group
爸爸与帕沙迪纳共青团共事
has truly been invaluable.
真是无法用钱来衡的
I hope y'all brought y'all appetites.
我希望你们带着好胃口来
Oh, yes.
是的
I brought mine.
我带来我的了
Oh, my goodness.
哦,天哪
This is much too much for me.
对我来说这太多了
I'll never get through all that.
我永远都解决不了全部那些
I have a little less here. I'll trade with you.
我这的少一点 我跟你换
Oh.
哦
Thank you.
谢谢
What, Charlene?
怎么了,夏琳?
Nothing, sir.
没事,先生
Oh.
哦
Oh, this food is so delicious.
哦,这食物真是太美味了
Serves him right, anyway,
在他右边服务,总之
makin' me wear this stinkin' outfit.
让我穿这讨厌的制服
You're very lucky to have found such talented help.
你很幸运能找到这么有才能的帮助
Well, our Ivy was with us for so long,
我们的长春藤跟着我们很久
we really thought of her as one of the family.
我们真的把她当成我们家庭的一分子
Mmm.
嗯
And after every meal,
在每顿饭后
my mother would scrape all the food we hadn't eaten
我的母亲会把我们没吃完的都收集起来
and put it on one big plate and give it to Ivy.
用个大盘子来盛,接着交给长春藤
Charlene...
夏琳...
what is that particular taste?
那特殊的味道是什么?
It's familiar, yet...
很熟悉,但是...
Is it some kind of herb like sage?
像是种像鼠尾草的香草?
No, it's sort of more like a milk of mint.
不,又有几分像是薄荷奶
Milk of... whatever it is, the taste is explosive.
什么奶...不管怎么样,味道真得不错
Mmm.
嗯
Well, good, then.
很好
Enjoy.
好好享用
Oh, just one moment.
哦,等一会儿
Uh, you know, uh,
嗯,你知道的,嗯
there's a lovely, sad Negro spiritual...
有首很好听的歌,忧愁的黑人精神
...that Ivy's brother used...
那是长春藤的兄弟常常唱的
Are you all right?
你没事吧?
Anyway, Ivy's brother used to sing this
长春藤的兄弟常常这样唱
when he came in from the tobacco fields.
当他从烟草地里回来时
Now, there's a second verse
现在,来第二部分
if you'd like to join in the chorus.
如果你们愿意一起来合唱
Dad?
爸爸?
Are you okay?
你还好吧?
I hope your father's all right.
我希望你们的爸爸没事
Does this happen often?
这常发生吗?
Well, if you'll excuse us.
请原谅
Um...
嗯...
Georgey, let's go watch that biography on Francis Drake.
乔治,我们去看关于法兰西斯德拉克传记
We... I mean,
我们...我的意思是
he seemed to be so moved by that song.
他看起来被那首歌打动了
Oh, he movin', all right.
哦,他感动中,没错
- And tonight's top story... - William?
今晚的头条新闻是... 威廉?
The FBI needs your help
联邦调查局需要你们帮助
in finding fugitive at large Charlene Morton.
来找出逃亡者夏琳摩顿
Charlene is an African-American female, 31 years of age...
夏琳是名非洲裔的美国女性,31岁...
What is it?
这是什么?
...and 5'6", 175 pounds,
...5英尺6英寸,175磅
with a tattoo on her left breast.
左乳房有纹身
Convicted of armed robbery,
犯有持械抢劫罪
Charlene is considered cunning and highly dangerous.
夏琳是即狡猾又十分危险的
Having escaped from the Women's Correctional Facility
6天前从洛杉矶外的一间
outside Los Angeles a mere six days ago,
女子监狱逃出
Morton is suspected to be armed.
摩顿怀疑是有武装的
This bank surveillance tape shows Charlene wielding a gun
银行的监视录影带显示夏琳正挥舞着枪
and holding a customer hostage.
并抓住一个消费者做人质
Charlene is considered dangerous and may be armed.
夏琳是危险人物,可能有武装
If you have any information concerning Charlene Morton,
如果你们有关于夏琳摩顿的任何消息
please contact your local FBI office.
请联系你们当地的联邦调查局
That's it for tonight's edition of "Criminals at Large."
这就是今晚的“在逃罪犯”
Good night and be safe.
晚安,小心点
Mrs. Arness, I can explain everything.
亚妮丝夫人,我能解释所有的事情
Pete, before you lose it, just let me explain.
彼德,在你误会前,请听我解释
There's nothing to say.
没什么好说的
But I didn't do it, Pete.
但我没做过,彼德
You have to get out.
你应该给我走
All right. I'll get my stuff.
好吧,我去收拾下我的东西
I don't understand. You saw her and where is she?
我不知道,你见过她,那她现在在哪儿?
I don't know where she is.
我不知道她在哪儿
Don't drop the soap.
别扔肥皂
What the hell does that mean?
那是什么鬼意思?
I just don't believe this. I'm worried about her.
我才不信这个,我在担心她
I hate the fact that she's out there all alone.
对于她独自一人在外的事实我觉得很厌烦
You're worried about the poor, innocent, frail creature
你担心那几乎不能在街上照顾自己的
who can hardly take care of herself on the street?
那可怜的、清白的、脆弱的人?
What about me? Tobias is gonna fire me!
那我呢? 托拜尔斯会解雇我的!
And another goody...
再说了
if Arness calls the cops, I could go to jail!
如果亚妮丝打电话给警察 我就会被送进监狱!
Here's the local number for the Bureau.
这是当地办公署的电话
The FBI takes harboring a fugitive very seriously.
联邦调查局处理逃亡者是很谨慎的
You, gentlemen, will be the first to hear from me.
你们,先生们,将首先收到我的讯息
Arness didn't call the cops, she called the FBI.
亚妮丝没报警,她报了FBI
- Now, you haven't seen me. - I have seen you.
现在,你没见过我 我见过了
No, I mean, you haven't seen me.
不,我的意思是,你没见过我
I'm looking right at you. What are you...
我正在看着你,你要...
If you do hear from her,
如果你有她的消息
please tell her the cool points are out the window and...
请跟她说冷却点在窗外...
she's got me all twisted up in the game.
她在游戏中已经击败了我
Why you messin' with Lene?
你为什么跟琳厮混?
I'm not messing with her, I'm helping her.
我没跟她厮混,我在帮她
Bullshit!
放屁!
Uh! I'm telling you the truth!
我来告诉你真相!
Listen up. You do not reopen this case.
听好了,你不用再掺和
From now on, I'm handlin' it for her.
现在起,我来处理
I'm not gonna reopen the case. The case is closed.
我不想再打开这盒子 盒子是关着的
Stay out of her life.
离她的生活远点
If I got to come back here, things are gonna get bloody.
如果我再回来这儿,那就会有流血事件
Maybe I should just finish this now.
也许我现在就应该把这解决掉
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
嗨,嗨,嗨
We have to find Charlene.
我们必须找到夏琳
I thought you hated Charlene.
我想你恨夏琳
I found out she's innocent.
我查出她是清白的
I knew it. I knew it.
我知道,我知道
Where am I gonna find her?
我要去哪儿找她啊?
Well, you can call her.
你可以打电话给她
How can I call her if I don't know where she is?
我不知道她在哪里,我怎么打电话给她?
I gave her your phone, in case you might...
我把你的电话给了她,万一你可以...
You gave her my new $600 titanium cellphone?
你把我那部600美元的新钛手机给了她?
Good idea. Come on.
好主意,来吧
W-What happened to your head?
你脑子怎么啦?
Metropolitan Museum of Art. How may I help you?
这是首都艺术博物馆 我能为您做点什么吗?
I know who set you up.
我知道谁陷害你
What?! Who?
什么?!谁?
Get in.
上车
So, what's up?
那么,怎么啦?
The guy points a gun to my head
那家伙用枪指着我
and tells me not to reopen the case.
叫我不要再打开那盒子
I'm thinking, "Why is he doing this?"
我在想,“他为什么要这么干?”
And then it dawns on me... it's because he was involved.
接着我有了头绪... 那是因为他是被牵连的
God damn him.
该死的他
I can't believe Widow did this to me.
我不敢相信威多这样对我
Where do you think he is?
你认为他在哪里?
I don't know.
我不知道
Probably downtown at this club he hang out at
有可能在市区他那间挂牌出售的夜总会里
called the Down Low.
叫做"堕落"
Got to get a confession.
去获取供词
You can't go there.
你不能去那儿
Eh, man, I'm serious.
我是认真的
A white man at the Down Low
白人到"堕落"
is either a cop, a corpse, or a crackhead.
就像是个警察,一具尸体,或是个笨蛋
You can't even talk 'hood.
你甚至不能吭声
I'll figure out something.
我能领会出些东西
Oh, and Howie told me to tell you
郝威要我告诉你
that "The cool points are out the window,
“冷却点就在窗外
and you got him all twisted up in the game."
你在游戏中已经击败他了”
Really?
真的?
That's the nicest thing anybody's ever said to me.
这是人们对我说过最好听的话
I'm gonna drop you off here
我会在这把你放下
because I got to get to the office for a conference call.
因为我要回办公室开电话会议
So, I'll see you in a little bit.
那么,我一会儿再见你
All right. Okay, cool.
好的
Yeah, freak boy, I need a ride.
是的,小子,我要部车
Can you come now?
你能现在来吗?
Damn. A straight, cold pimp.
见鬼,直走,蠢货
Looks like Gendler beat us to her.
看起来像是钱德勒为她来打击我们
I can assure you, Mrs. Arness,
我能向你保证,亚妮丝夫人
Peter Sanderson is no longer affiliated
彼德山德森不会再跟
with Tobias, Kline, and Barnes.
托拜尔斯、,克莱恩和巴恩斯有关联
Good.
很好
You have great ankles.
你的脚踝很棒
What?!
什么?!
Were you a dancer?
你曾是个舞者?
Yeah... well, yes. I was.
是的
I bet you had great presence.
我想你曾经有很多的观众
Oh. How you two doin'?
你们俩干什么?
I hope I'm not interruptin' anything.
我希望没打搅了什么
You're nasty.
你真下流
W-What are you doing here?
你在这儿干什么?
Please, Mrs. Arness, I'm not here to cause any trouble.
亚妮丝夫人,我来这儿不是来找麻烦的
Well, that would be a first.
那一定是头一回
Julia? Julia?
茱莉亚? 茱莉亚?
Julia a little tied up right now.
茱莉亚现在有点累了
I just need you to hear me out.
我只想你听听我说的话
Peter is not responsible for any of this. I am.
彼德不需为任何这些负责,而是我
I mean, the guy is a great lawyer.
我的意思是,这家伙是个很棒的律师
And he's one of the most decent men I've ever known.
我没见过像他这么正派的男人
- I doubt that's saying much. - Shut up, fool.
我想那说得过多了 闭嘴,蠢货
If only you knew the lengths he's willing to go to
如果你仅仅知道他的自愿去
to help a friend.
帮助朋友的时间长度
Listen... sister...
听着...修女...
"Sister"?
"修女"?
Why don't you go back to Sanderson,
你为什么不回到山德森那儿
and the "Jungle Fever" thing the two of you got goin' on,
你们俩得了"丛林热"
before I call the cops?
在我报警之前?
That's it, pretty boy.
很好,帅哥
You ever met the big hurt?
你没被狠扁过?
The who?
谁?
I wouldn't do that if I were you!
我是你可不会那么做!
And why not?
为什么不呢?
You'll be instantly returned to prison, where you belong.
你应该回到你本该所属的监狱
All right. That's it.
没错
How dare you!
你疯了!
To hell with what I just said.
没听清我刚说的
You obviously one of them hard learners.
你显然是个听力有障碍的人
Howie?
郝威?
This is my house! I will not be told to do what I...
这是我家!我不想说那些
William.
威廉
I'm Kate Sanderson. Have you seen my kids?
我是凯特山德森,你见到我的孩子们了吗?
- Over there. - Oh!
在那儿 哦!
Hey!
嘿!
Oh, God!
哦,上帝啊!
What is going on?
怎么了?
It's just the FBI, Mom.
就是联邦调查局的,妈妈
Yeah, they're just doing a, like, search.
他们就是来,像是,调查
For what?
查什么?
Well, for Charlene. But she's not...
查夏琳,可她不...
The FBI is looking for your nanny?
联邦调查局在找你们的保姆?
Man, take your hands off me!
伙计,把你的手拿开!
I said, back off me, punk!
我说,退后,蠢货!
That's what I mean. You know what I'm sayin'?
那就我的意思,你知道我在说什么吗?
You don't want none of this, now.
我不希望这样吧
Excuse me...
劳驾...
Homeboys...
小伙子...
Say, yo. You got a bathroom in there?
嗨,你在那儿有间浴室?
Say, yo, what's the dealio?
嗨,干什么呢?
Mmm. Who's your daddy?
你爸爸是谁?
Back that booty up and put it on the glass.
把战利品搞回来,放进玻璃杯中
Anybody here dig what I'm sayin'?
这儿有人明白我说什么吗?
So...
那么...
your nanny was doing time...
你们的保姆...
for armed robbery.
犯有持械抢劫
And then she broke out of prison...
她逃狱出来...
...and then she came here.
然后就来到这儿
But she's innocent...
但她是清白的
and now your dad has gone off to...
现在你们的爸爸是去...
help her.
帮她
Sounds crazy, right?
听起来挺疯狂的,是吗?
He's not the same guy anymore.
他不再是那个同样的人了
Yeah, he's really cool.
是的,他真的很酷
Say, any of you homies holdin' extra Jimmy High?
说说看,你们在家 也这么兴奋高兴?
'Cause I'm all about crunchin' some of that boofanny tonight.
我晚上可是来狂欢的
If you harm one hair on that dog's head...
如果你伤到那只狗头上的一根毛发
Yeah, "Harm a hair on the head." You got me all nervous.
好了,“伤到头上的一根毛法” 你让我十分的紧张
Hello?
喂?
- Sarah? - Oh, hey, Charlene.
莎拉? 哦,嗨,夏琳
Put your daddy on the phone.
叫你爸爸听电话
No, he's not here. He went out to find you.
他不在,他去找你了
He went to find me?!
他去找我?!
Tsk. All right.
好吧
Howie, flip a "U." We headed downtown.
郝威,调个头,我们回市区去
Downtown's where I live, precious.
我就住在市区,抓紧了
No! No!
不!不!
Whoa!
喔啊!
What's on your mind, player?
你在想什么,伙计?
What's with you? You been drinkin' some "Hatorade"?
那你呢?你是喝了"哈托拉"吧?
What's up, Flavor? Where you from?
怎么啦,伙计?你从哪儿来?
From the 'hood and misunderstood.
打该来的地方来
- How's your pimp hand, dog? - Strong, baby, strong.
搞啥呢,伙计? 强啊,小子,强
Can you swerve, snowman?
你能突然转向吗,雪人?
Do I got "honky" spray-painted on my forehead?
我前额上有写着“白鬼子”?
Of course I can. I'm tryin' to peep a bowwow.
当然我行,我试着来窥视一下
If you so at home, man, then dance with the woman.
如果你觉得是在家一样,伙计 就跟这女人跳舞吧
I can't. I got b'ness.
不行,我有很大只的
Go on out there and get your groove on.
到那儿去,秀出你的最佳状态
No, I can't. I got important b'ness to take care of.
不,我不行,我有要紧的事情要顾及
I tell you, but...
我跟你说,但是...
You'll get a life sentence for this.
为此你会被判无期徒刑
You're a kidnapper and a whore!
你是个绑匪,还是个淫妇!
Hey. Keep talkin', tea bag.
继续说啊,茶叶带
Ooh?! Tea bag!
哦?!茶叶带!
Yeah, you'll be gummin' your bubbles.
是的,你在冒着黏糊糊的泡沫
Yeah, oh! Terrible.
太可怕了
Damn, boy, you lookin' all kind of stupid.
见鬼,伙计,你看起来真是蠢
Really?
真的?
'Cause I got this outfit from your mama.
因为我是从你妈妈那儿弄来的这套装备
Yo, Eminem, cut the wigger shit.
好了,阿姆,别说胡话了
I don't think you know how much trouble you in.
我想你不知道你遇到多大麻烦了
Fine, fine, fine.
很好,很好,很好
I'm here to talk business...
我来这儿是来谈事的
private business.
私事
What fresh air is this?
这是什么地方?
I don't see him anywhere.
我没看到他
I think he's in that back room over there.
我想他在后面那间房里
What do we do with Her Majesty?
那我们怎么来处理她呢?
Sit down.
坐下
What?
什么?
Sit it on down.
坐下去
Now, look, if you move,
听着,如果你跑了
your little Willy gonna be bridged down.
你的小东西就活不成了
- You dig? - Dig.
明白了? 明白
All right. Come on.
好吧,走吧
Is that real?
那是真的?
Oh.
哦
Uh, Seven and Seven, double.
嗯,七加七,双倍
How you doin'?
你怎么样?
What?!
什么?!
I said, "How you doin'?"
我说,“你怎么样?”
Oh, fantastic.
哦,幻想
You either the dumbest cracker I ever met or you straight up...
你或者是我遇见过最闷的闷瓜 或者是你就是...
Hold that thought. I love this song.
等等,我喜欢这首歌
Turn that off.
关掉
Get everybody up out of here.
叫这儿的所有人都出去
I'm telling you, he is definitely in there.
我要告诉你,他真的在那
Okay, all right, so he's in there,
好,没错,他在那儿
and then you go in, and then what happens?
然后你进去了,接着发生了什么?
Three seconds.
3秒钟
Why you here?
你为什么在这儿?
I got a feeling you're sitting on a hefty sum of stolen cash.
我感觉到你与被盗的巨款有关
You want to hide it, you need a lawyer.
你想把其隐藏起来,我想你需要一个律师
What's with the phone?
电话怎么了?
I'm calling in the cavalry.
我在召集骑兵
You'll go back to prison.
你会重回监狱的
So you wanna help me launder my money?
那么你想帮我洗黑钱了?
I can hide it in an untraceable account
我可以把它存进一个 不易被人发现的帐号里
in the Cayman Islands.
在鳄鱼岛
All I want is $ 100,000.
我想要的是10万美金
We both walk out of here wealthier men.
我们能一起走出这儿
And I tell you where Charlene is... that simple.
我会告诉你夏琳在哪里...那很简单
You wearin' a wire?
你在走钢丝?
Me?
我?
No. Are you?
不,你呢?
Then... then they kidnapped me.
然后,他们绑架了我
And they took my dog, William.
他们带走了我的狗,威廉
That's a damn shame.
真是可恶
Oh, you don't care.
喔,你不介意
You smokin', Grandma?
你抽烟吗,奶奶?
Why not?
为什么不呢?
To hell with your proposition.
让你的鬼话见鬼去吧
Hold it. Charlene is ready to roll over on you.
冷静,夏琳已经准备反咬你一口
She knows who your accomplice was.
她知道谁是你的同党
- Oh, that's pretty funny. - I'm not kidding.
哦,那真是很有趣 我没开玩笑
They're out in the parking lot waiting for my signal and...
他们就在外头停车场里等着我的信号 然后...
and... and... and the signal is...
然后...然后...信号就是...
if I don't come back, they call the FBI.
如果我没回来,他们就给FBI打电话
There was no accomplice, fool.
那儿没有同党,蠢货
There was a girl in the photo.
在照片里有个女孩
No, there was somebody in a wig and a dress.
不,那是有人假扮的
You...
你...
You left her clothes, the gun, and the money.
你丢下她的衣服,枪,还有钱
See?
明白了?
You just too damn smart for your own good.
你真是他妈的聪明
Look, we can't wait no more.
听着,我们不能再等下去了
Wait, wait. Charlene!
等等,夏琳!
Open up. Widow wanna see me.
开门,威多想见我
Says who?
谁说的?
Says Lene.
琳说的
Pete.
彼德
Well, ain't this a psychic moment?
好了,这不是精神时刻?
I was just comin' to see you.
我正想见到你
Come on, Widow. This is between me and you.
好啊,威多,这就关乎你和我
Let him go.
让他走
No problem.
没问题
Ugh!
啊!
Oh, shit.
哦,见鬼
What... come on, now. What are you doin'?
怎么了?你要干什么?
Ugh!
啊!
I got it.
我拿到了
- Aim it, aim it, Howie! - Yeah!
瞄准,郝威! 没错!
Uh-huh! Who got the gun now, huh?
啊哈!现在枪在谁手里,啊?
Who got that gun now? Homie, that's right.
谁现在拿着枪? 很好
Get y'all asses on the ground!
全部给我趴下!
Asses on the ground where I can see 'em, huh?
快给我趴下!
Take him out!
带他出去!
Pussies.
姑娘们
Wasn't that fun?
很有趣,不是吗?
I'm just gonna roll up on out of here.
我刚想离开这儿
Thank you.
谢谢
- Aah! - FBI!
FBI!
Everybody, freeze!
所有人,不许动!
Charlene! Charlene! Oh, baby!
夏琳! 夏琳! 哦,亲爱的!
Oh, oh, baby.
哦,哦,亲爱的
Charlene.
夏琳
Son of a...
见鬼
Drop it!
放开!
Oh, Charlene.
哦,夏琳
What?
什么?
Damn, dog.
该死的
Hey, Howie, she's all right.
嗨,郝威,她没事
Charlene...
夏琳...
I...
我...
Do me a favor, precious.
帮我个忙,亲爱的
Don't ever scare me like that again,
不要再那样吓我了
or I'm gonna have to give you a nasty spanking,
否则我可就要打你的屁股
if I'm not being too subtle.
如果我不装成那么敏感的话
He's such a damn freak.
他真是个怪人
Are you Sanderson?
你是山德森?
Yeah.
是的
Wait, wait. She's innocent.
等等,她是清白无辜的
Save it.
说话注意点
I can prove it.
我能证明
Mr. Sanderson... that was pretty ballsy.
山德森先生...很有胆量
You'd make a hell of an agent.
你冒了很大的风险,干得漂亮
Oh, thank you very much, but I don't think I did anything
哦,十分感谢,但我想我并没做什么
- an ordinary man wouldn't do... - Thanks again.
一个普通的人是不会... 再次感谢
Mr. Sanderson...
山德森先生...
There you are.
你在这
You have behaved abonidably.
你行为可憎
Aboni...
可...
Abomidably.
可恨
- Abodi... - Abominably.
可恶
I know.
我知道
- Shakespeare.
莎士比亚
No, wait. This is serious.
不,等等,这很严肃
And I'll have you dis...
我要你...
disboweled.
取出肠子
Uh, disballed.
嗯,取消资格
Dis...
取消...
Disbarred?
取消律师资格?
Disbarred.
取消律师资格
Oh, to hell with it.
哦,通通见鬼去吧
I do believe I'm stoned.
我想我是醉了
Just don't tell anybody you ever saw me like this.
不要告诉任何你现在瞧见我这模样
Mrs. Arness...
亚妮丝夫人...
William.
威廉
Oh, God, you are an ugly dog...
哦,上帝啊,你是只难看的狗
and heavy.
还很沉
Here, I got him.
我来抱
Thank you.
谢谢
Is there a 24-hour diner around here?
这附近有24小时餐厅吗?
I know where one is. I'll take you there.
我知道有个地方有,我带你去
I'm dreadfully hungry.
我真是太饿了
You guys okay?
你们没事吧?
What do you think?
你认为呢?
Yo, be cool, G-mo.
唷,真酷,走了
Yo, out back, G-mo.
唷,真酷。
Full cheesy, homey.
少来了
Well, that's not good enough.
好吧,那还不够好
You'll just have to keep trying, won't you?
你会继续试下去,不是吗?
I called Arness four times. She'll only talk to Peter.
我给亚妮丝打了四次电话 她只跟彼德讲话
Well, we're just gonna have to keep him around.
我们应该把他带出来
Oh, hey, guys.
哦,伙计们好
Peter.
彼德
Did I mention I'm going out on my own?
我提过我要自己一个人出去干吗?
You don't have the resources.
你没有资金
Well, I have one multibillion-dollar client.
我有个拥有数十亿财富的客户
It's a start.
这是个开始
And a partner.
还有个合作者
I'm all over it, G.
我都收拾好了
Let's go.
我们走
Excuse me.
劳驾
Peter, we can talk about this.
彼德,这我们能谈谈
Ed, you can kiss my natural black ass.
没门
Peter...
彼德...
Ashley, who are you doing here?
艾希莉,你跟谁在这儿?
Oh, I was, uh, meeting, uh, uh...
哦,我是在,嗯,开会,嗯...
- for my aunt's estate. - About her aunt's estate.
是关于我姑妈的不动产 关于她姑妈的不动产
There was a codicil.
有份遗嘱
Well, say goodbye to half your stuff.
那么,说再见吧!
I'll call you.
我会给你电话的
Lookin' good, kids. Almost there.
嘿,孩子们,找些好的 差不多都在那了
Peter, your 4:00 is waiting for you in your office.
彼德,你有人在办公室等你,是4点的预约
I don't have any meetings today.
我今天没有没有安排任何会见
I'm sorry. I didn't realize I had an appointment.
抱歉,我忘了,我有个约会
Hey.
嗨
So, this is how a big-time tax attorney lives, huh?
瞧,这就是一个一流的律师的生活,嗯?
This place is big pimpin', P. Diddy.
这地方很无足轻重
- How you doin'? - I'm a'ight.
你好吗? 我很好
I really wanted to tell you again
对你为我做的一切
how much I appreciate what you did for me.
再次表示感谢
If I could only give you back half of what you've given me.
如果我可以把你给我的一半还你就好了
Please. We'll call it even. Now give me a hug.
我们称那是平等 好吧,给我个拥抱吧!
Hey, white people don't hug.
嘿,白人是不拥抱的
You ain't white.
你不是白人
Well, I'm off-white.
呵,我是灰白的
Good to see you.
见到你很高兴
Kate...
凯特...
Hi.
嗨
Um, oh, well, I'm, uh...
嗯,哦,我...
I got to finish up some things with Howie.
我找郝威办点事
Oh, Kate, this is Charlene. Charlene, this is Kate.
哦,凯特,这是夏琳 夏琳,这是凯特
Hi. You've certainly been shaking things up around here.
嘿,你在这儿会把事情给闹大的
Well, shakin' is what I do best.
呵呵,那是我的强项
It's a pleasure to meet you, Kate.
很高兴认识你,凯特
Thank you.
谢谢
And take care of him for me.
帮我好好照顾他
Hi.
嗨
So...
那么...
what... what brings you down?
是什么把你带到这来的?
I mean, you know, not what brings you down,
你知道,我的意思并不是指 是什么东西使你想来这?
but, I mean, what brings you down here?
我的意思是,你为什么会来这呢?
Well, I was just wondering, um...
嗯,我只是想知道...
how often do you take that shortcut past my house?
你多久会走这条捷径,经过我家?
Technically?
技术上的?
Uh, well...
嗯...
uh, pretty much every day.
呃,每天都有很多次呢
Well, you know, technically...
你知道的,那是技术上的...
That's stalking.
那叫围捕
It's kind of cute.
那是种装腔作势
Kate...
凯特
There's something I want to say to you.
嘿,我有事要告诉你
The cool points are out the window,
冷却点就在窗外
and I'm all twisted up in the game.
我已做好准备加入这场游戏了
What does that mean?
那是什么意思呢?
It means I love you.
那表示我爱你
Rastaman, hold still, or you're gonna have
紧紧抓住
these Jamaican beads all over the floor.
否则这些牙买加珠子会掉一地的
Yeah, here we go.
好了,别担心
All right, halfway done.
好了,完成一半了
What you think?
你怎么想?
Holler at your boy.
对你的孩子发牢骚
- Hey. - Nothin' is nothin'.
嘿 没有的事
Who's your daddy now?
现在谁又是你的父亲?
Boy, you are some kind of freaky.
你真让人捉摸不定